administrative I tell everyone should be done with 73 now if you're not done I
행정 난 당신이 내가 일을하지 않는 경우 모두가 지금 73 수행해야 말해
think you're late and you're in trouble
당신이 늦게 당신은 문제가 있다고 생각
Muslim graves will be out very soon we're still going through them and there
이슬람 무덤은 우리가 아직도 그들을 통해 가서 거기에있어 매우 곧 될 것입니다
are basically I think done but we have to double check a few things I will send
기본적으로있는 내가 다 생각하지만, 우리는 내가 보낼 것 몇 가지를 한 번 확인해야
them out
그들을 밖으로
ok so in terms of reminding you where we are in the class I last looked very
확인 그래서 우리는 클래스에 당신을 생각 나게 측면에서 어제 아주 보였다
briefly at segmentation we looked at some soft attention models substation
간단히 분할에서 우리는 약간의 부드러운주의 모델 변전소 보았다
models are away for selectively paying attention to different parts of the
모델은 선택적으로 다른 부분에 주목 떨어져있는
image as your processing it was something like a recurrent neural
당신의 처리와 같은 이미지는 재발 신경과 같은했다
network so glad you selectively pay attention to some parts of the scene and
네트워크 다행 당신이 선택적으로 장면의 어떤 부분에주의를 지불하고
enhance those features and will start about special transformer which is this
이러한 기능을 강화하고이되는 특수 변압기에 대해 시작됩니다
very nice way of basically in a different way cropping parts of an image
이미지의 일부를 자르기 다른 방법으로 기본적으로 아주 좋은 방법
or some features either in a hydrogen or in any kind of warped shape aren't in
또는 수소 또는 변형 된 모양의 모든 종류의 하나 일부 기능에없는
like that so very interesting kind of PC that you can slot internal network
당신은 내부 네트워크를 슬롯 수 있습니다 PC의 때문에 매우 흥미 종류 등
architectures so today we'll talk about videos
아키텍처는 그래서 오늘 우리는 동영상에 대해 얘기하자
specifically now in image classification you should be familiar by now whether
구체적으로 현재 이미지 분류에서 이제 여부에 의해 잘 알고 있어야합니다
the basic combat set up you have an image that comes in a reprocessing it to
기본적인 전투는 당신이 그것을 재 처리 (A)에 오는 이미지가 설정
for example classified in a case of videos we won't have just a single image
동영상의 경우 분류 예를 들어 우리는 단지 하나의 이미지가되지 않습니다
but will have multiple frames so this is an image of 32 by 32 will actually have
이 실제로있을 것이다 (32)에 의해 32의 이미지가 그래서하지만 여러 프레임을해야합니다
an entire video frames so 32 by 32 mighty purty a sometime extent ok so
전체 동영상은 32 강 이뿌다 언젠가 범위 그래서 확인에 의해 그래서 32 프레임
before I dive into how we approach these problems with I'd like to talk about
나는 우리가 I와 이러한 문제를 접근하는 방법에 뛰어 전에 대해 이야기하고 싶습니다
very briefly about how we used to address them for calm asking about using
우리가 진정 사용에 대해 문의를 해결하기 위해 사용하는 방법에 대한 매우 간략하게
pcr-based methods so some of the most popular features right before coming to
오른쪽에 오기 전에 그래서 가장 인기있는 기능 중 일부를 방법을 PCR 기반
work today became very popular where these dense trajectory features
이 조밀 한 궤적 특징 곳 일 오늘은 매우 인기가
developed by hanging at all and I just like to give you a brief taste of
모든 매달려 개발 한 난 그냥 당신에게 간단한 맛을주고 싶어
exactly how these features worked because it's kind of interesting and
정확히 어떻게 가지 흥미로운 때문에 이러한 기능이 근무하고
they inspire some of the later developments in terms of how come to
그들은 온 방법의 측면에서 나중에 개발의 일부를 영감
show that works actually operating videos so in this trajectory is what we
이 궤도에 그래서 실제로 작동하는 비디오를 작동 쇼는 무엇이고 우리
do is we have this video the playing and we're going to be detecting these key
이렇게 우리는이 비디오 재생이되고, 우리는 이러한 키를 검출 할거야
points that are good to track in a video and then we're going to be tracking them
좋은 점은 비디오에서 추적하고 우리는 그들을 추적 할거야
and you end up with all these little track let's that we actually track
당신은 모든 작은 트랙 결국 우리가 실제로 추적하는 것을하자
across the video and then lots of features about those track let's and
그 트랙하자 약 기능의 영상 다음 제비에서
about the surrounding features that accumulated just crimes so just to give
에 대해에게 단지 범죄를 축적 주변 기능, 그래서 그냥주는
you an idea about how this worked there are basically three steps roughly we
당신은 어떻게에 대한 생각은 세 단계는 우리가 기본적으로이 대략있는 일
detect feature points at different scales in the image I'll tell me briefly
이미지에 서로 다른 규모에서 특징점을 검출 나는 나에게 간단히 말씀 드리죠
about how that's done
그 어떻게하는지에 대한
then go to track those features over time using optical flow methods optical
다음 광 광류 방법을 사용하여 시간이 지남에 따라 그 기능을 트랙으로 이동
flow method solved explain very briefly they basically give you a motion field
흐름 방법은 매우 간단하게 설명 해결 그들은 기본적으로 당신에게 운동 필드를 제공
from one thing to another and they tell you how the scene moved from one frame
한 가지에서 다른 그들은 장면이 하나의 프레임에서 이동하는 방법을 알려
to an extent Xtreme and then we're going to extract a whole bunch of features but
어느 정도 익스트림 다음 우리가 기능의 전체 무리를 추출거야하지만,
importantly we're not just going to extract those feature set fixed
중요한 것은 우리는 단지 고정하는 기능 세트를 추출하지 않을거야
positions in the image but we're actually going to be struck me
이미지에 위치하지만 우리가 실제로거야 나를 공격한다
speechless and the local coordinate system every single track let and so
말을하고 로컬 좌표 시스템은 모든 단일 트랙하자 등
these histogram of greedy insist gotta flows and and be resource we're going to
욕심 이러한 히스토그램 돼 흐름을 주장하고 우리가 가고있는 자원이 될
be extracted them in the coordinate system off a track wit and so hard here
열심히 여기 트랙 재치 떨어져 좌표계를 추출 할 수
we saw histograms gradients and two-dimensional images are basically
우리는 히스토그램 구배 및 2 차원 화상은 기본적으로봤을
generalizations of that too
그 일반화 너무
videos and so that's the kind of things that people used to encode the
비디오 및 그래서 사람들이를 인코딩하는 데 사용되는 물건의 종류입니다
spatio-temporal bombings in terms of the key point detection part there's been
키 포인트 검출부의 관점에서 공간 - 시간 폭탄 테러가있었습니다
quite a lot of work on exactly how to detect good features and videos to track
좋은 기능과 추적하는 비디오를 감지하는 방법을 정확하게에 작업 꽤 많은
and intuitively you don't want to track a video that are too smooth because he
직관적으로 당신은 그가 때문에 너무 부드러운 있습니다 비디오를 추적하지 않도록
can't log onto any visual feature as there are ways for basically getting a
기본적를 취득하기위한 방법이 임의의 시각 기능에 로그인 할 수 없습니다
set of points that are easy to track and a video so there are some papers on this
이에 대한 몇 가지 서류가되도록 추적하고 비디오하기 쉬운 점 세트
so you detect a bunch of features like this
그래서 당신은이 같은 기능의 무리를 검출
optical flow algorithms on these videos
이 동영상에 광학 플로우 알고리즘
take a frame and a second frame and it will solve for a motion field
프레임 및 제 2 프레임을 그리고 모션 필드 해결할 것
displacement vector at every single position in to where it traveled for how
이 방법은 여행 곳에서 모든 단일 위치에서 변위 벡터
the free moved as I hear some examples of optical flow results
내가 광학 플로우 결과의 몇 가지 예를 들어으로 무료 이동
basically here every single pixel is colored by a direction in which that
기본적으로 여기에 모든 단일 픽셀은 방향에 의해 착색되는 것을
part of the image is currently moving into video so for example this girl has
이는 예를 들어자가 갖도록 이미지의 부분은 현재 영상으로 이동
all yellow meaning that you probably translating horizontally or something
아마 당신은 수평 또는 뭔가 변환하는 모든 노란색 의미
like that the two most common methods for using optical flow for computing it
추천 그것이 컴퓨팅 광학 흐름을 사용하기위한 두 가지 일반적인 방법
at least me one of the most common ones here as blocks from boxing Malik that's
권투 말리크에서 블록으로 여기에 가장 일반적인 적어도 나 하나
the one that is kind of like a defaulting to use so if you are
그래서 당신이 경우에 사용하는 디폴트로 같은 종류의 인 하나
computing optical flow in your own project I would encourage you to use
자신의 프로젝트에 광학 흐름을 계산하는 것은 내가 사용하는 것이 좋습니다 것
this large displacement optical flow method so using this optical flow we
이 큰 변위 광학 플로우 방법은 그래서이 광 흐름이 우리를 사용하여
have all these key points using optical flow we know also have the move as we
우리가 알고있는 광학 플로우를 사용하여 모든 주요 장소로는 우리로 이동을했습니다
end up tracking these lil truckloads of may be roughly fifteen frames at a time
한 번에 약 십오 프레임 일 수있다 이러한 릴 트럭 분량을 추적 끝
so we end up with these half a second roughly track lets through the video and
그래서 우리는이와 끝까지 0.5 초 정도 트랙이 비디오를 통해 할 수 있습니다 및
then we encode
우리는 인코딩
regions around this track what's with all these descriptors and then went to
모든 이들 기술자와의 어떤이 트랙 주변 지역에 갔다
accumulate all these visual Peterson two histograms and people used to play with
함께 플레이하는 데 사용되는 모든 피터슨 시각이 히스토그램 사람들을 축적
different kinds of like how do you exactly truncate video specially because
정확히 특별히 때문에 비디오를자를 어떻게 같은 다른 종류의
we're going to have a histogram an independent histogram and every one of
우리는 히스토그램을 독립적 히스토그램과의 모든 일을 할 겁니다
these business and then we're going to basically create all these histograms
이러한 비즈니스 다음 우리는 기본적으로 모든 히스토그램을 만들거야
urban with all these visual features and all of this thing goes into an SVM and
이러한 모든 시각적 기능을 갖춘 도시와이 일을 모두가 SVM에 가서
what kind of the rock a layout in terms of how people address these problems in
사람들이 이러한 문제의 해결 방법의 측면에서 바위 레이아웃의 종류
the past your truck just think of it as is going to be fifteen frames and it's
트럭 단지로 생각 과거는 다섯 프레임이 될 것입니다 그리고 그것은이다
just XY positions so a 15 X Y coordinates the strangled and then we
단지 XY 위치 그렇게 15 XY는 다음 교살 및 좌표 우리
extract in the local coordinate system now in terms of how we actually approach
우리가 실제로 접근 방법의 관점에서 현재 로컬 좌표계 추출
these problems with that works she never called Alex net on the very first layer
그와 함께 이러한 문제는 그녀가 첫 번째 층에 알렉스 그물을 호출되지 작동
will receive an image thatís for example 227 227 by three and
세에 의해 예를 들어 227 (227)에 대한 이미지 thatís을 받게되며
reprocessing it with 96 filters that are 11 by 11 applied it's right for and so
11 11 96 필터를 재 처리하면 오른쪽에 대한 등의 적용
we saw that with Alex net this results in the 5555 by ninety six volume in
우리는 알렉스 그물이 아흔여섯 볼륨에 의해 5555 결과 보았다
which we actually have all these responses of all the filters at every
우리는 실제로 각에서 모든 필터의 모든 응답을 갖는
single spatial position so now what would be a reasonable approach if you
하나의 공간적 위치 당신이 경우 합리적인 방법이 될 것입니다 무슨 지금
wanted to generalize accomplish all that work into a case we don't just have a
우리는 단지이없는 경우에 작동하는 모든 작업을 수행 일반화하고 싶어
220 somebody turns 23 but you may be happening frames that you like to encode
220 누군가가 23집니다하지만 일이 될 수는 인코딩 좋아하는 프레임
so you have an entire block of 227 227 battery by 15 that's coming in to
그래서 당신은에오고 그 15 227 227 배터리의 전체 블록이
accomplish all that work you're trying to echo the both the spatial and
달성 당신이 공간을 모두 에코하려는 일을 모두하고
temporal patterns and inside this little block of volume so would be like one
시간적 패턴과 볼륨이 작은 블록 내부 그래서처럼 될 것이다
idea for how to change accomplish all that work
변경하는 방법에 대한 아이디어는 모든 일을 성취
generalize it to this case
이 경우에 일반화
and arrange them as like two blocks ok that's interesting I would expect that
나는 것으로 기대 확인 그 흥미로운 두 블록 등 그들을 배치
do not work very very well so the problem with that is kind of interesting
그게 문제가 관심의 종류 그래서 아주 아주 잘 작동하지 않는다
basically all these neurons are looking at only a single frame and then by the
기본적으로 모든 신경에 의해 다음 단 하나의 프레임에서 찾고있다
end of the comment that you end up with you on that are looking at a larger and
당신이 당신과 함께 결국 주석의 끝이 그에 큰보고하고,
larger regions and your challenge so eventually these neurons with see all of
더 큰 영역과 도전 그래서 결국 모두 볼 이러한 뉴런
your input but they would not be able to very easily relate
귀하의 의견하지만 그들은 아주 쉽게 연관 할 수 없을 것입니다
like little special control patch in this image so I'm not sure actually
이 이미지에서 조금 특별한 제어 패치 같은 사실은 확실하지 않다
really good idea did you turn them into it I think so we'll get to some of those
정말 좋은 아이디어는 내가 그래서 우리는 그 중 몇 가지를 얻을 수있을 거라 생각 그것으로 만들어 놓을 않았다
that do something like that
그 같은 일을
take 45 channels effectively and you could put a comment on that so that's
효과적으로 45 채널을 가지고 그, 그래서 당신은에 코멘트를 넣을 수
something that all get to I think you could do that I don't think it's the
모든 I에 도착 뭔가 당신은 내가는 생각하지 않는 것을 할 수 있다고 생각
best idea as a yes so you're saying that things in one slice of this time are you
그래서 당신이 시간의 한 조각의 일이 당신을 것을 말을하는지 예 '로 최고의 아이디어
want to extract similar kinds of features in one time then a different
다음 다른를 한 번에 기능과 유사한 종류의 압축을
time
시각
similar to the motivation of doing it sharing with specially because peter is
피터이기 때문에 특별히 공유 그 일의 동기 부여와 유사
here are useful down there as well so you have the same kind of property where
여기에 당신이 재산 곳의 같은 종류 그래서뿐만 아니라 거기 유용
you'd like to share weights and time not only in space
당신은 공간뿐만 아니라 무게와 시간을 공유하고 싶습니다
ok so building on top of that idea of the basic thing that people usually do
확인 그래서 사람들이 일반적으로 수행하는 것이 기본 일의 아이디어 위에 구축
when they want to apply commercial networks and videos as they extend these
그들은 이러한 확장으로 상용 네트워크와 비디오를 적용 할 때
filters not only to don't only have filters in space but you also have these
필터는 공간 필터를하지뿐만 아니라 할 수 있지만 이러한이
filters and extend them small amounts in time so before we have 11 Bielema
필터 우리가 Bielema (11)가 전에, 그래서 시간에 그들에게 소량의 확장
filters
필터
1111 by tea filters where Tia some small temporal extent so say for example we
몇 가지 작은 시간 정도 그렇게 예를 들어 말 티아 차 필터에 의해 1111 우리
can use a to up to 15 in this particular case he was 30 2011 by three filters and
세 가지 필터에 의해 그는 2011 년 30이었다 특히이 경우 최대 15로 사용할 수 있습니다 및
then by three because we have RGB and so basically these filters are now you're
다음 세 가지에 의해 우리는 RGB를 가지고 있기 때문에 기본적으로이 필터는 당신이있어 지금
thinking of sliding filters not only in space and carving out an entire
뿐만 아니라 공간에서 필터를 슬라이딩 생각하고 전체를 조각
activation map but you're actually sliding filters not only in space but
활성화지도하지만 실제로뿐만 아니라 공간에서 필터를 슬라이딩하고 있지만,
also in time and they have a small finite temporal extent in time and you
또한 시간에 그들은 시간에 작은 유한 한 시간 정도가 있고
end up carving out an entire activation volume ok so you're introducing this
당신이 도입하고, 그래서 확인 전체 활성화 볼륨을 조각 끝
time to mention into all your kernels and to all the are dying stages have an
시간은 모든 커널에 모든 죽어가는 단계에 언급하기를
additional time to mention along which were performing the convolutions so
그래서 회선을 수행 된 따라 추가 시간이 언급
that's usually how people extract the features and then you get this property
그 사람들이 기능을 추출하는 방법 일반적으로 그리고 당신은이 속성을 얻을
where safety is three here and so so then when we do the spatial temporal
안전 그래서 여기에 등 세 곳에 우리는 공간적 시간적를 수행 할 때
competition we end up with this parameter sharing scheme going in time
경쟁 우리는이 매개 변수를 공유하는 방식은 시간가는 결국
as well as you mentioned so basically what extent all the filters and time and
뿐만 아니라 당신이 그렇게 기본적으로 언급 한 바와 같이 어느 정도 모든 필터 시간과
then we do convolutions not only in space but also in time
우리는 공간뿐만 아니라 시간뿐만 아니라 회선을
wind up with activation volume activation maps so some of these
활성 볼륨 정품 인증과 바람은 그래서 이들 중 일부 매핑
approaches were proposed quite early on for example one of the earlier ones
접근 방식은 이전의 것들의 예를 하나 아주 초기에 제안했다
for activity recognition is maybe from 2010 so the idea here was that this is
활동 인식이 2010 년부터 아마이기 때문에 아이디어는 여기가 있음을했다
just a couple of work but instead of getting a single input of sixty by 40
일의 대신 (40)에 의해 예순의 단일 입력을 받고 단지 몇
pics also we are getting in fact seven frames of sixty by forty and then their
사진은 또한 우리는 마흔에 의해 사실 예순 일곱 프레임을 받고 자신의
conclusions are three deconvolution as we refer to them so these filters for
우리가 그래서 이러한 필터들을 참조로 결론은 세 디컨 볼 루션 있습니다
example might be sold by seven but now by three as well as we end up with a 3d
예를 들어뿐만 아니라 우리가 3 차원으로 끝낼 같이 세 가지로 이제 일곱 판매 될 수 있지만
calm and the three conditions are applied at every single stage here
진정과 세 가지 조건은 여기에 모든 단일 단계에서 적용됩니다
similar paper also from 2011 but the same idea we have a block of friends
2011 년 비슷한 종이하지만 같은 생각 우리는 친구의 블록을
coming in and you promised them with 3d completions three-dimensional filters at
들어오는 당신은 3 차원 완료 입체 필터에서 그들을 약속
every single point in this commercial network so this isn't 2011
이 상용 네트워크에있는 모든 단일 지점 그래서이 2011 아니다
very similar idea also so these are from before actually Alex next these
매우 유사한 아이디어도 그렇게이 다음이 전에 실제로 알렉스 출신
approaches are kind of like smaller know that work accomplished all that work so
접근 방식은 일이 그렇게 모든 작업을 수행하는 것이 작은 알고 같은 종류의 수 있습니다
the first kind of large-scale application of this was from this
이러한 대규모 애플리케이션의 제 1 종이 출신
awesome paper in 2014 by capacity at all
용량에 의해 2014 년 멋진 종이의 모든
this is for processing videos so the model here on the very right that week
이 처리 동영상을 여기에 바로 오른쪽에있는 모델이 주 그래서
we called slow fusion that is the same idea that I presented so far these are
우리는 내가이는 지금까지 그렇게되게 같은 생각 느린 융합이라고
three-dimensional competitions happening in both space and time and so that's
세 가지 차원 모두 시간과 공간에서 일어나는 경쟁 때문에 그건
slow fusion as we refer to it because you're slowly using this temporal
느린 융합 천천히이 시간을 사용하고 있기 때문에 우리는 그것을 참조로
information just as before we were slowly using the spatial information now
단지 우리는 이전과 정보는 천천히 이제 공간 정보를 사용하고
there are other ways that you could also why are up comedy show networks and just
당신은 또한 왜 코미디 쇼 네트워크 및 그냥있는 수있는 다른 방법이 있습니다
to give you some context historically this is Google research and Alex let's
몇 가지 컨텍스트를 제공하는 것은 역사적으로이 구글의 연구이며, 알렉스하자
just came out and everyone was super excited because they work extremely well
그냥 와서 그들이 매우 잘 작동하기 때문에 모두가 슈퍼 흥분했다
images and I was in the video analysis team at Google and we wanted to run on
이미지와 나는 구글 비디오 분석 팀에 있었고, 우리는에 실행하고 싶었다
the YouTube videos and but it was not quite clear exactly how to generalize
유튜브 동영상하지만 그것은 일반화하는 방법을 정확하게 꽤 명확하지 않았다
you know commercial networks and then just to videos so we explored several
우리는 여러 가지 탐구 그래서 당신은 동영상을 다음 상용 네트워크와 알고
kinds of architecture stuff how you can actually wear this up so floats no
당신이 실제로 그래서 수레이를 착용하지 수있는 방법 건축 재료의 종류
fusion as a 3d called kind of approach early fusion is this idea that someone
접근 조기 융합의 종류라는 차원으로 융합는이 아이디어 사람
described earlier where you take a chunk of friends and just woke up need them
필요할 친구의 덩어리를 가지고 그냥 일어 났을 경우 앞에서 설명한
long channels you might end up with a 227 227 by like 45
긴 채널은 45 등에 의해 227 227으로 끝낼 수 있습니다
everything is just stocked up and you do a single column over it so it's kind of
이 종류의, 그래서 모든 것이 사들이고 당신은 그 위에 하나의 열을
like your filters on the very first call later have a large temporal extent but
맨 처음 통화하여 필터처럼 나중에 큰 시간적 범위를 가지고 있지만
from then on everything else is two-dimensional competition in fact we
다음 다른 모든부터 사실 두 차원의 경쟁은 우리
call it early because he refused the temporal information very early on in
그는 매우 초기에 시간 정보를 거부했기 때문에 일찍 전화
the very first letter from then on everything just to call you can imagine
다음 모두에의 첫 번째 편지는 당신이 상상할 수있는 호출
architecture is likely convolution so here the ideas would take to Alex nets
아이디어 알렉스 그물에 걸릴 여기 있도록 아키텍처는 가능성 회선입니다
we place them say ten things apart so they both computed independently on
우리는 그들을 떨어져 10 가지 그들이 그렇게 모두 독립적에 계산 말할 배치
these 10 points apart and then we must be much later in the fully connected
이 10 점을 따로 따로 그리고, 우리는 완전히 연결에 많은 이상이어야합니다
layers and then we had a single claim baseline that is only looking at a
레이어, 그리고, 우리는 단지보고 단일 청구 기준을했다
single frame of the video so you can play with exactly how the white wire up
비디오의 한 프레임은 그래서 당신은 정확히 흰색 선까지로 재생할 수 있습니다
these models look Asian model you can imagine that they've had three
이 모델은 그들이 했어 상상할 수있는 아시아 모델을 보면 세
dimensional colonels now the first layer you can actually visualize them and
차원 대령은 이제 첫 번째 층은 실제로 그들을 시각화 할 수 있으며,
these are the kinds of features you end up learning on videos these are
이 다음은 동영상에 당신이 학습 결국 기능의 종류입니다
basically features that were familiar with except they're moving because now
그들은 지금 때문에 이동하는 것을 제외하고 잘 알고 있었다 기본적 기능
these filters are also extended a small amount and time to have these little
이 필터는이 작은을 가지고 소량 및 시간을 연장된다
moving blobs and some of them are static and some of them are moving and they're
블롭을 이동하고, 그들 중 일부는 정적이고, 그들 중 일부는 이동 그들이있어
basically detecting motion on the very first layer and so you end up a nice
기본적으로 첫 번째 층에 움직임을 감지하고 그래서 당신은 멋진을 종료
moving bombings
폭탄 테러 이동
question is how much we'll get to that and I think the answer is probably yes
문제는 우리가 그에게거야 얼마나 내가 대답은 예 아마 생각
just as in spatial it works better if smaller filters and you have more depth
단지 공간에서이 경우 더 작은 필터를 작동하고 당신은 더 깊이가
at the same applies I think in time and we'll see an architecture that does that
같은 적용에 나는 시간에 생각하고 우리 것을 수행하는 아키텍처를 볼 수 있습니다
mean but expecting
의미하지만 기대
classifying so we have a video and were still classifying number of categories
이렇게 분류 우리는 영상이 여전히 카테고리의 수를 분류 한
at every single frame but now you're not only function that single frame but also
매 프레임에서 그러나 지금 당신은 단지 하나의 프레임 것이 아니라 작동하지 않는
a small number of frames alot on both sides so maybe your prediction is
프레임 소수 어쩌면하여 예측이 양쪽 alot을
actually a function of safety drinks a half a second video to end up with fun
실제로 안전의 기능은 반에게 재미와 끝까지하는 제 2 비디오 음료
moving pictures in this paper also released video they said over one
본 논문도 발표 동영상을 동영상을 그들은 하나 이상했다
million videos and 500 classes just a given context for why this is actually
이 실제로 이유에 대한 백만 동영상과 500 클래스는 주어진 컨텍스트
it's kind of difficult to work with videos and right now I think because
이 동영상 작업을 가지 어려운 지금은 내가 있기 때문에 생각
problem right now i think is that there's not too many very large-scale
문제는 지금 내가 생각이 너무 많은 매우 큰 규모가 아니다 것입니다
datasets like millions of very varied images that you see an image that there
당신은 이미지 것을 볼 매우 다양한 이미지의 수백만 같은 데이터 세트가
are no really good equivalent of that in the video domain and so we tried with
비디오 영역에서 그 어떤 정말 좋은 동등하지 않으며 그래서 우리는 함께 노력
this for status and back in 2013 but I don't think it actually we fully achieve
이것은 그러나 2013 년 상태 및 다시 내가 그것이 실제로 우리가 충분히 달성 생각하지 않습니다
that and I think we're still not seeing very good really lost the assassin
그와 나는 우리가 여전히 정말로 암살자을 잃었 아주 좋은 표시되지 않는 생각
videos and that's partly why we're also slightly discouraging some of you from
비디오 및 그 우리는 또한 약간에서 당신의 일부를 낙담하는 이유 부분적이다
working on this on projects because you can't retrain these very powerful
프로젝트에이 작업은 이러한 매우 강력한을 재교육 할 수 없기 때문에
features because the data sets are just not quite there another kind of
기능 데이터 세트는 단지 확실히 거기에 다른 종류이기 때문에
interesting things that you see and this is why we also sometimes caution people
당신이보고 우리가 때때로 사람을주의 이유는 흥미로운 것들
from working on videos and getting very elaborate very quickly with them because
그 때문에 매우 빠르게 매우 정교을 동영상에 작업 점점에서
sometimes people think they have videos and get very excited if they want to do
때때로 사람들은 동영상이 그들이 수행하려는 경우 매우 흥분 생각
3d color shows Alice teams and they just think about all the possibilities that
3d 컬러 앨리스 팀을 표시하고는 모든 가능성에 대해 생각
opened up for them but actually turns out that single frame methods are a very
그들을 위해 개방 실제로 단일 프레임 방법은 매우 것을 밝혀
strong baseline and I would always encourage you to run that first so don't
강력한베이스와 나는 항상 첫 번째를하지 않는 실행하는 것이 좋습니다 것
worry about the motion in your video and just try single frame that works first
동영상의 움직임에 대해 걱정하고 단지 첫 번째 작품 하나의 프레임을 시도
so for example in this paper we found that a single from baseline was about
그래서이 논문의 예를 들어 우리는베이스 라인에서 하나에 대한 것을 발견
59.3% classification accuracy in our dataset
우리의 데이터 세트에서 59.3 %의 분류 정확도
and then we tried our best to actually take into account small local motion but
다음 우리가 실제로 계정 작은 지역의 움직임을 고려하기 위해 최선을 시도했지만
we ended up bumping down by 11.6% so all this extra work all the extra computer
우리는 11.6 %에 의해 아래로 당김이 모든 추가 작업 모든 여분의 컴퓨터 그래서 결국
and then you ended up with relatively small gains I'm going to try to tell you
그리고 당신은 내가 당신에게 시도거야 상대적으로 작은 이익에 결국
why that might be a basically video is not always as useful as you might
그가 될 이유 기본적으로 비디오는 항상 당신이하는만큼 유용하지 않다
intuitively think and so here are some examples of kind of predictions that we
직관적으로 생각하고, 그래서 여기에 예측 종류의 몇 가지 예입니다 그 우리
are different data sets of sports and our predictions and I think this kind of
스포츠와 우리의 예측 다른 데이터 세트는 내가 이런 종류의 생각
highlight slightly why adding video might not be as helpful in some settings
강조 약간 이유에 비디오를 추가하는 것은 일부 설정에서와 같이 도움이되지 않을 수도 있습니다
in particular here if you're trying to distinguish sports and think about it
여기에 특히 당신은 스포츠를 구분하고 그것에 대해 생각하려고하는 경우
trying to distinguish say tennis from swimming or something like that it turns
이 회전처럼 수영이나 뭔가에서 테니스 말을 구별하려고
out that you actually don't need very fine local motion information if you're
당신이 있다면 당신은 실제로 아주 좋은 지역의 움직임 정보를 필요로하지 않는 것을
trying to distinguish tennis from swimming right lots of blue stuff lots
파란색 물건을 많이 오른쪽 많은 수영에서 테니스를 구별하려고
of red stuff like the images actually have a huge amount of information and so
빨간색 물건의 이미지가 실제로 정보의 엄청난 금액을 가지고과 같이
you're putting in a lot of additional parameters and trying to go after these
당신은 추가 매개 변수를 많이 넣고이 후 이동하려는
local motions but and most in most classes actually be local motions are
대부분의 클래스의 대부분은 실제로 지역 운동은하고 있지만, 지역 운동
not very important they're only important if you have very fine-grained
매우 중요하지 그들은 당신이 매우 세분화 된 경우에만 중요한 것
categories where the small motion actually really matters a lot as a lot
작은 움직임이 실제로 정말 많은으로 많은 문제 카테고리
of you if you have videos you'll be inclined to use spatial temporal crazy
이 동영상이 경우 당신은 미친 시간적 공간적 사용하는 경향됩니다
video networks but I think very hard about is that locomotion extremely
비디오 네트워크 그러나 나는 그 운동이 매우 약 열심히 생각
important and you're setting because if it isn't you might end up with results
중요하고 그렇지 않은 경우 결과를 얻을 수 있기 때문에 당신은 설정하는
like this where he put in a lot of work and it may not work well let's look at
그는 작업을 많이 넣어 곳이 같은 그것은 잘 작동의를 살펴 보자되지 않을 수 있습니다
some other video classification that works so this is April 2015 its
작동 다른 비디오 분류 그래서 이것은 2015 4월 자사의
relatively popular it's called sea 3d and the idea here was basically your
상대적으로 인기가 그것은 바다 3d 및 아이디어라고 여기에 기본적이었다 있어요
network has this very nice architecture its three-month recalled and two by two
네트워크는 두 가지로이 아주 좋은 그 3 개월 불러 아키텍처와 두가
pool throughout the idea here is that cool let's do the exact same thing but
여기에 생각에 걸쳐 풀 멋진의 정확한 같은 일을 할 수 있다는 것입니다하지만,
extend everything in time so going back to your point you want very small
시간에 모든 확장하므로 지점으로 돌아가는 당신은 매우 작은합니다
filters so this is everything is three my tree might recall to buy to buy to
이 모든 세 가지입니다 때문에 필터가 내 나무를 구입하는 구입 기억 수도 있습니다
pool throughout the architecture so it's a very simple kind of big united in 3d
아키텍처 전반에 걸쳐 풀은 그래서 차원에서 큰 미국의 매우 간단한 종류의
kind of approach and that works reasonably well and you can look at this
접근 방식의 종류 및 그 합리적으로 잘 작동하고 당신이 볼 수
paper for reference
참조 용 종이
another form of approaches actually that works quite well as from Karen Simonian
접근 방법의 또 다른 형태는 실제로는 카렌 시몽에서로 아주 잘 작동합니다
in 2014
2014 년
Simonian by the way as the same he's a person who came up with the BG not he
같은과 같은 방법으로 그는 BG하지 그가 해낸 사람의 SIMONIAN
also has a very nice paper on video classification and the idea here is that
또한 비디오 분류에 아주 좋은 종이를 가지고 있으며 여기에 생각이 있다는 것입니다
he didn't want to do three dimensional competitions because it's kind of
이 종류의 때문에 그는 세 가지 차원의 경쟁을하고 싶지 않았다
painful to have it
그것을 가지고 고통
98 or find it and so on so he only used to measure compilations but the idea
98 그것을 발견하고 너무 너무에 그는 단지 컴파일하지만 아이디어를 측정하는 데 사용
here is that we have to come that's looking at an image and the other one is
여기에 우리가 와서해야 할 이미지를 찾고, 다른 하나는 점이다
looking at optical flow of the video so both of these are just images but the
이 두 단지 이미지 만 너무 비디오의 광학 흐름에 있습니다보고
optical flow basically tells you how things are moving in the in the image
광학 흐름은 기본적으로 상황이 이미지의 이동 방법을 알려줍니다
and so both of these are just kind of like an avg net like or Alex not like
그래서이 둘은 평균 그물 같은 또는 알렉스 싫어하는처럼 그냥 가지입니다
that one of them another close one of them on the image and you extract
그 중 하나의 이미지에 이들의 또 다른 가까운 하나가 추출이
optical flow with say the Bronx method before and then you let the UF use that
광학 흐름은 전 브롱스 방법을 말한다 다음은 University of Florida의 사용을 허용하는
information very late in the end so both of these come up with some idea about
아주 늦은 결국 이렇게 두 가지의 정보를 몇 가지 아이디어에 대해 생각해
what they are seeing in terms of the classes in the video and then refused
다음 그들이 비디오의 클래스의 관점에서보고있다 및 거부
them and there are different ways of using them so they found for example
그들이 그들이 예를 찾을 수 있도록 그들을 이용하는 방법은 다양
that if you just use a special comments are only looking at images you get some
당신은 그냥 특별한 코멘트는 이미지를 찾고 사용하는 경우 당신은 몇 가지를 얻을
performance if you use come on just the optical flow it actually performs even
방금 광 흐름에 와서 사용하는 경우 성능이 실제로도 수행
slightly better than just looking at the raw images
단지 원시 영상을보고보다 약간 더
optical flow actually here in this case contains a lot of information and then
이 경우 실제로 여기 광 흐름은 정보를 많이 포함
if you actually end up even better now an interesting point to make here by the
실제로 의해 여기 수 있도록 더 나은 지금 흥미로운 점을 끝낼 경우
way is that if you have this kind of architecture especially here
방법은 당신 특히 여기 아키텍처의이 종류가있는 경우
complex history much by three filters you might imagine that actually would
세 가지 필터에 의해 많은 복잡한 역사는 실제로 것이라고 상상할 수
think that I mean why does it help to actually put an optical flow you'd
나는 그것이 실제로 당신이 좋겠 광학 흐름을 넣어하는 데 도움 않는 이유를 의미한다고 생각
imagine that in the center and framework we're hoping that these comments learn
중앙 및 프레임 워크에 우리가 이러한 의견 배울 것으로 기대하고 상상
everything from scratch in particular they should be able to learn something
특히 처음부터 모든 것을 그들이 뭔가를 배울 수 있어야합니다
that simulates the computation of computing optical flow and it turns out
즉, 광학 흐름을 계산하는 계산을 시뮬레이션하며 밝혀
that that might not be the case because sometimes when you compare video
때때로 비디오를 비교할 때 때문에 그 경우하지 않을 수 있음
networks on only the hospital and then it works better and so I think the
만 병원에 네트워크 및 그것은 잘 작동 그래서 내가 생각
reason for that is probably comes back to actually data since we don't have
우리가 가지고 있지 않기 때문에 그 이유는 아마 실제로 데이터로 회복된다
enough data we have small amount of data I think you actually probably don't have
충분한 데이터 우리가 당신이 실제로 아마이없는 생각 데이터의 소량
enough data to actually learn very good optical flow like features and so that
충분한 데이터가 실제로 기능 등 같은 아주 좋은 광학 흐름을 배울 수
would be my particular answer why actually hard getting up to go to the
실제로 하드에 갈 점점 왜 내 특정 대답을 것
network is probably helping out in many cases if you guys are working on your
너희들이에서 작업하는 경우 네트워크는 아마 대부분의 경우에서 돕는 당신의
project with videos I would encourage you to actually try to be this kind of
내가 실제로 시도하는 것이 좋습니다 것입니다 비디오와 프로젝트는 이런 종류의 일하기
architecture
건축물
optical flow and then pretend that it's an image and you could come to an end to
다음 광학 흐름과는 이미지의 척 당신은에 끝이 올 수
that seems like a relatively reasonable approach ok so so far we've only talked
즉, 상대적으로 합리적인 접근 방식처럼 좋아 보인다 그래서 지금까지 우리는 얘기했습니다
about the little local information in time right so we have these little
시간의 작은 지역 정보에 대한 권리 그래서 우리는이 작은이
pieces
조각
black half a second ever tried to take advantage of it should be better
블랙 0.5 초 적 좋을한다 활용하려
classification but what happens if you have videos that actually have much
실제로 많은이 동영상이 경우 분류하지만 무슨 일이
longer
더 길게
temporal kind of dependencies that you like to model so it's not only that the
당신이 모델 같은 종속의 시간적 종류 그래서 그건뿐만 아니라 그
local motion is important but actually there are some events throughout the
지역 운동은 중요하지만 실제로 어떤 이벤트가 걸쳐있다
video that are much larger in time scales in your network and they actually
비디오 네트워크와 실제로의 시간 규모에서 훨씬 더 큰 것을
matter so event to happening after event one can be very indicative of some class
문제 때문에 이벤트 이후에 발생하는 이벤트는 하나 몇 가지 클래스의 매우 나타낼 수 있습니다
and you'd like to actually model that would work so are the kinds of
당신이 실제로 그 모델이 그렇게 일하는 것이하려는 종류의은
approaches that you might think for trying to actually you know how would
실제로 당신은 얼마나 알고에 당신이 노력에 대해 생각하는 것이 접근
you mind actually model these kinds of much longer-term events
당신은 훨씬 더 긴 기간 이벤트 이러한 종류의 모델을 실제로 될까요
ok so attention model perhaps so you may be like to have any tension over you're
당신이있어 위에 어떤 긴장감을 가지고 같은 확인하므로주의 모델은 아마도 그래서 당신은 할 수있다
trying to classify this entire video maybe like to have a tension over
이 전체 비디오를 분류하려고하는 것은 어쩌면 통해 긴장을 갖고 싶어요
different parts of the video
비디오의 다른 부분
yeah that's a good idea I see so you're saying that we have these multiscale
그래 그게 내가보고 좋은 생각이 그래서 당신은 우리가 이러한 다중 스케일을 가지고 말을하는지이야
approach is where we process images on very low detail level but also sometimes
우리는 때때로 매우 낮은 상세 수준에 이미지를 처리​​하지만 어디 방법이다
we resize the images and process them on the global level as a maybe the frames
우리는 이미지의 크기를 조정하고 아마 프레임으로 글로벌 수준에이를 처리
we can actually like speed up the video and put a comment on that I don't think
우리는 실제로 비디오의 속도를 내가 생각하지 않는에 코멘트를 넣어 원하는 수 있습니다
that's a very common but it's senator sensible idea I think yeah so the
나는 그래서 네 생각은 매우 흔한 일이지만 상원 의원 재치있는 아이디어
problem roughly is that basically this extent is maybe ten times too short it
문제는 대략 것을 기본적으로이 정도가 아마 열 번 너무 짧은 그것입니다
doesn't spent our many seconds so how do we make architectures that are
그래서 우리의 초를 소비하지 않는 방법을 우리가 아키텍처를 어떻게해야합니까
functional much longer time scales and their prediction
기능 훨씬 더 긴 시간 규모 및 예측
yes the one idea here is we have this video and we have different classes that
예 여기에 하나의 아이디어는 우리는이 동영상을 가지고 있으며 우리는 다른 클래스가 그
would like to predict at every single point in time but we want that
시간에 모든 단일 시점에서 예측하기 좋아하지만 우리는 것을 원하는 것
prediction to be a function not only a little choked up 15 seconds but actually
예측 함수가 될 조금까지 숨 막혀 15초뿐만 아니라 실제로하기
a much longer time expense so the idea that is sensible as you actually use
당신이 실제로 사용으로 분별있는 생각 때문에 훨씬 더 긴 시간 비용
record while at work somewhere in the architecture because your current
기록 작업에서 어딘가 현재 때문에 건축에있는 동안
networks allow you to have infinite context and principal over everything
네트워크는 당신이 모든 것을 통해 무한 상황과 주체를 가질 수 있도록
that has happened before you up till that time especially if you go back to
당신이 돌아갈 특히 최대 그때까지 당신을하기 전에 그 일이있다
this paper that I've already showing you in 2011 it turns out that they have an
이미 2011 년을 보여주는 한이 논문 그것은 그들이이 밝혀
entire section where the cheek take this and they actually have analyst team that
전체 섹션 뺨이 걸릴 그들은 실제로 분석 팀이 곳
does exactly that this is a peep from 2011 using 3d called NLST I'm so way
내가 그렇게 방법이야이 NLST라는 차원을 사용하여 2011에서 들여다가 있음을 정확히 수행
before they will call in 2011 and so this paper basically has it all
그들은 2011 년에 호출 그래서이 논문은 기본적으로 모두가 전에
the model little local motion with 3d calm and they most model global motion
3 차원 침착하고 대부분의 모델 글로벌 모션 모델 작은 지역 운동
with Ella stance and so they put a stamp on the play the full connected layers so
엘라 자세 등으로 이들은 전체 연결 층 때문에 플레이에 스탬프를 넣어
they strung together fully connected layers with this recurrence and then
그들은 다음이 재발와 완전히 연결 층을 함께 중독
when you're predicting classes every single frame you have infinite context
당신은 모든 단일 프레임 클래스를 예측 할 때 당신은 무한 컨텍스트가
this paper is as I think quite ahead of its time and it basically has it all
나는 꽤 시대를 앞서 생각하는이 논문이며, 그것은 기본적으로 모든 권한을 가지고
except it's only set at 65 times I'm not sure was not more popular I think people
이 단지 65 시간에 설정되어 제외하고 나는 사람들이 더 많은 인기를 생각하지 않은 확실하지 않다
are basically this is way ahead of its time paper that recognizes both of these
기본적으로이 이들 모두를 인식하는 방법 앞서 시간 종이입니다입니다
national team sweat before I even knew about them so since then and there are
국가 대표팀 땀 나는 심지어 그 이후 그들에 대해 알고있다 전에
several more recently percent actually kind of take a similar approach so in
몇 가지 최근 %는 실제로 가지에서 매우 유사한 접근 방식을
2015 by Jeff Donahue at all from Berkeley the idea here is that you have
제프 도나휴 2015은 모든 버클리에서 여기에 아이디어는 가지고있다
video you like to again
비디오 다시에 좋아
classify every single frame but they have these comments that look at
매 프레임을 분류하지만 그들은 보면 이러한 의견이
individual frames but then they have also Alice team that string this
각각의 프레임은하지만 그들은 또한 앨리스는 해당 문자열 팀 한이
together temporarily a similar idea also from a paper from I think this is Google
함께 일시적으로 나는이 구글이다 종이에서도 비슷한 생각 생각에서
and so the idea here is that they have optical flow and images are processed by
그래서 여기에 아이디어는 광학 흐름을 가지고 이미지를 처리​​하는 것입니다
complex and then again you have analyst am that merges that over time so again
복잡하고 다시 당신은 시간이 지남에 그렇게 다시 병합 애널리스트 오전이
this this combination of local and global so so far we've looked at kind of
로컬 및 글로벌이이 조합은 그래서 지금까지 우리는 어떤 종류의 검토 한
two architectural patterns in accomplishing your classification that
당신의 분류를 달성 두 아키텍처 패턴이
actually takes into account important information modeling locomotion which
실제로 계정 중요한 정보 모델링 운동에 소요되는
for example beast entry to call for use optical flow or look more global motion
예를 들어 짐승 항목은 사용 광학 플로우를 요구 이상의 전역 움직임을 볼 수 있습니다
where we have chemistry together sequences morning time steps or fusion
여기서 우리는 화학 함께 시퀀스 아침 시간 단계 또는 융합이
of the two now actually I like to make the point that there's
두 사람은 지금 실제로 나는이 있다는 점을 확인하는 등의
another cleaner very nice interesting idea that I saw in a recent paper and
내가 최근 논문에서 본 다른 청소기 아주 좋은 흥미로운 아이디어와
then I like much more and so here's basically the rock picture of what
그때는 훨씬 더 좋아하고 그래서 여기에 기본적으로의 바위 그림 무엇
things look like right now we have some video and we have a 3d come that say
지금 우리가 일부 비디오를 가지고 같은 것들을 우리는 차원이 말을 그 온 보일
that is using optical flow may be ordered using 3d column or both on the
그 사용 광학 플로우는 차원 열 또는 둘 모두를 사용하여 주문할 수 있습니다
trunk of frame crank up your data and then have are nestled atop unfortunately
프레임의 트렁크는 데이터를 크랭크 후 불행하게도 꼭대기에 자리 잡고있다 한
or something like that that are doing the long-term modeling and so kind of
또는 장기 모델링을하고 그 그 때문에 종류의 같은
kind of not very nice are unsettling about this is that their son of this
이 약의 종류 아주 좋은되지는 불안하다 그이 자신의 아들
ugly asymmetry about these components to have these parties neurons inside the 3d
이러한 구성 요소에 대한 추악한 비대칭이 당사자에게 3 차원 내부의 신경 세포가하는
come that are only a fraction of some small local chunk of video and then you
당신은 비디오의 몇 가지 작은 지방 덩어리의 일부입니다 그 와서
have these neurons in the very top that our function of everything in the video
맨 이러한 신경 세포가 그 비디오의 모든 우리의 기능
because their record units that are a function of everything that's come
올 모든 일의 함수 자신의 기록 단위 때문에
before it and so it's kind of like an unsettling asymmetry or something like
그 전에 그래서 그것은 불안 비대칭 또는 뭔가처럼 같은 종류의
that so there's a paper that has a very clever any idea from a few weeks ago
그래서 몇 주 전에에서 매우 영리한 어떤 생각을 가지고 종이가있다
that is much more nice and homogeneous lifestyle where everything is very nice
모든 것이 아주 좋은 곳이 훨씬 더 좋은 균일 한 라이프 스타일입니다
and margins and simple and so I don't know if anyone can think of how we could
어떻게 우리가 할 수 있었던 사람이 생각할 수있는 경우 마진과 간단하고 그래서 난 몰라
but we can do to make everything much more cleaner and I couldn't because I
하지만 우리는 모든 것을 훨씬 더 청소기를 만들기 위해 할 수 있습니다 내가 할 수 없었던 나는 때문에
don't come up with this idea but I thought it was cool what I read it
이 아이디어를 제공하지만 난 그것을 읽고 무엇 멋진라고 생각하지 않습니다
before the comment actually starts processing the images not sure what that
주석이 실제로 어떤 것을 확실하지 않은 이미지 처리를 시작하기 전에
would give you see would have torn asunder optical information and comments
당신이 찢어진 것 참조 산산이 광 정보 및 의견을 줄 것이다
on top that somehow you would certainly have neurons that are function of
어떻게 든 당신이 확실히의 함수이다 신경을 것 위에
everything but it's not clear what the US team will be doing in that case
그것은하지만 모든 미국 팀이이 경우에 일을해야 될지 분명하지 않다
likely to be blurring the pixels it's too low level probably processing at
아마에서 처리 너무 낮은 수준의 픽셀을 흐리게 될 가능성이
that point then there's a lot of media like an intolerable that works
그 시점은 다음 작품을 참을 같은 미디어를 많이있다
differently temporal resolutions that this problem is looking every bit you
이 문제는 모든 비트를 찾고 있음을 다르게 시간적 해상도
another time that is looking like every trip every a friend and I say so your
모든 모든 여행 친구처럼 보이는 내가 그래서 당신의 말을 또 다른 시간
ideas that I think it's similar to what someone pointed out where you take this
나는 당신이이 걸릴 경우 다른 사람이 지적한 것과 유사한 생각 아이디어
video and you work on multiple scales on that video to speed up the video when
비디오 당신은 때 비디오를 빠르게 해당 동영상에 여러 저울에서 작동
you slow down the video and then you have 3d come that's on the front row
당신은 비디오를 느리게 그리고 당신은 그 앞줄에있어 온 3D했습니다
like speeds or something like that it's a sensible idea can you do background
그것은 현명한 생각이 같은 속도 또는 뭔가처럼 배경을 수행 할 수 있습니다
subtraction only look at things are interesting to look at I think that's a
일을보기 위하여 흥미에 내가 그는 생각에 빼기 만 보면
reasonable idea I think it kind of goes against this idea of having end-to-end
내가 생각하는 합리적인 생각은 종류의 엔드 - 투 - 엔드를 갖는이 아이디어에 반하는
learning because you're introducing like this explicit computation that you think
당신은 당신이 생각하는이 명시 적 계산과 같이 소개하고 있기 때문에 학습
is useful as he got
그가 가지고로서 유용
sharing between the 3d comes out and they are and that's interesting I'm not
3 차원 사이에 공유가 나오고 그들이 그 재미의 내가 아니에요
a hundred percent sure because the Arnon is just hittin state vector and matrix
아르 논 때문에 확실히 백퍼센트는 상태 벡터와 행렬을 잤다된다
multiplies and things like that but in a calm players we have disliked spatial
곱셈과 사물처럼하지만 진정 플레이어에서 우리는 공간을 싫어했다
structure I'm not actually sure how the sharing would work but yeah ok so the
구조 나 공유가 작동하는 방법을 실제로 모르겠지만 그래 좋아하므로
idea is that we're going to see we're going to get rid of the are now we're
아이디어는 우리가 우리가있어 지금 없애하는거야 보게 될 것이다
going to basically take on that and we're going to make every single neuron
기본적으로이에 걸릴 것 우리는 모든 단일 신경 세포를 만들거야
and that comes out to be a small recurrent neural network like every
그 모든 같은 작은 재발 성 신경 네트워크로 나온다
single neuron becomes recurrent in the calm that ok so the way this will work
하나의 신경 세포가 확인하는 방식 때문에이 작동합니다 진정에 재발된다
and I think it's a beautiful but their picture is kind of a kind of ugly so
그리고 나는 그것이 아름다운 생각하지만, 자신의 사진이 그렇게 추한의 종류의 종류
much for this makes no sense so let me try to explain this in a slightly
많은이 말도 안돼 위해 이렇게 나를 약간이 설명하려고하자
different way what we'll do instead is that we have a caller somewhere in the
우리가 대신 무엇을 할 거 야 다른 방법은 우리가 어딘가에 발신자를 가지고있다
neural network and it takes input from below the operative a previous calmly or
신경 네트워크가 수술 이전에 침착 아래에서 입력을 받아 또는
something that we're doing competitions over this to compute the output at this
우리는이를 통해 경쟁을하고있는 일이의 출력을 계산하기
layer right so the idea here is we're going to make every single come a little
여기에 아이디어는 우리가 매일 조금 오는 만들려고하고있다 우측 있도록 층
later a kind of a recurrent player and so the way we do that is we just as
나중에 때문에 재발 플레이어의 종류 우리가 할 길을 우리가 그대로입니다
for we take the input from below us and we do comes over it but we also take our
에 대한 우리는 우리 아래에서 입력을 받아 우리는 그 위에 오는 않지만 우리는 또한 우리를 취할
previous output from the previous time instead of this
대신 이전 시간으로부터 이전 출력
players out there so that's this caller from previous time step in addition to
그 외에도 이전 시간 단계에서이 발신자 그래서 거기 플레이어
the current input that this time stuff and we do competitions over both this
이 때 물건과 우리가 모두이 이상 대회를 수행하는 것이 현재의 입력
one and that one and then we kind of have you know we don't call when we have
하나 하나, 그리고, 우리는 종류의 우리가 우리가있을 때 호출하지 않습니다 알고있다
these activations from current input and activations from our previous outfit and
이전 복장에서 현재 입력하고 정품 인증에서 이러한 활성화 및
we add them up or something like that we do recurrent like that work like merge
우리는 그들을 추가하거나 우리가 병합 같은 그 일처럼 재발을 수행하는 것이 같은
of those two to produce are up and so we're a function of the current input
그 두 생산의 최대이며, 그래서 우리는 현재의 입력의 기능이야
but also a function of our previous activations if that makes sense and so
뿐만 아니라 이전 활성화의 기능은 너무 감각을 만드는 경우
it's very nice about this is that were in fact only using two-dimensional
그것은이 두 차원을 사용하여 사실이었다 즉 대해 아주 좋다
competitions here and there is no 3d count anywhere because both of these are
여기에 대회 이들 모두는 어디 때문에 더 차원 수는 없다
width by height by depth rights of the previous convo liam is just with highly
이전 야그의 리암의 깊이 권한에 의해 높이로 폭은 매우 함께
depth from the previous layer and we are with high depth from previous time and
이전 계층의 깊이와 우리는 이전 시간에서 높은 깊이있는
some of these are two-dimensional competitions but we end up with kind of
이들 중 일부는 두 가지 차원 대회하지만 우리는 종류와 끝까지
like recurrent process in here and so one way to see this also with recurrent
재발 여기에 프로세스 등 하나의 방법처럼 재발과이를 볼 수 있습니다
neural networks which we looked at is that you have this recurrence where
우리가 바라 보았다 신경망은이 재발 위치를 가지고있다
you're trying to compete in state and it's a function of your previous state
당신은 상태에서 경쟁하기 위해 노력하고 있으며 이전 상태의 함수이다
and the current attacks and so we looked at many different ways of actually
현재 공격은 그래서 우리는 실제로 여러 가지 방법으로 보았다
wiring up that recurrence so there's a velar por el esteem or the GRU which GRU
연구 개의 포 엘 존중가 그래서 그 재발 또는 GRU GRU까지 배선
is a simpler version of LSD and if you recall but it almost always has similar
LSD의 간단한 버전입니다 당신이 기억하지만 경우는 거의 항상 비슷한 있습니다
performance to analyst team so GRU a slightly different update formulas for
분석 팀에 성능이 약간 다른 업데이트 수식에 대한 GRU 그래서
actually performing that recurrence and see what they do in this paper is
실제로이 논문은에 무엇을 그 재발을 수행하고 참조
basically they take the GRU because it's a simpler version of an Austrian that
이 오스트리아의 간단한 버전이기 때문에 기본적으로 그들은 GRU을 그
works just as well but instead of every single matrix multiply it's kind of like
단지뿐만 아니라 대신 모든 단일 매트릭스 작동하는 것은 일종의처럼 곱
replaced with a calm if you can you can imagine that every single matrix
진정으로 대체 당신은 당신이 상상할 수있는 수 있다면 그 모든 단일 행렬
multiply here just becomes a call so we can evolve over our input and become
여기에 곱하면 바로 전화가 그래서 우리는 우리의 입력을 통해 발전 할 수지고가
involved a large output and that's the before and the below and then we combine
큰 출력을 포함하고는 이전의와 아래, 그리고, 우리는 결합
them with the recurrence just us in the GRU to actually get our activations and
다만 미 GRU의 재발과 그들이 실제로 우리의 활성화를 가져올 수 및
so before it looked like this and now it just looks like that so we don't have
이 같은 모습과 지금은 그냥 보이는 전에 그래서 우리는이 없습니다
some parts of the internet and extent of some parts finite we just have this our
일부 지역의 인터넷과 범위의 일부는 우리가 그냥이이 유한 한 우리의
income that where every single layer is returned its computing but it before but
소득은 모든 단일 층 전에하지만 컴퓨팅하지만 반환되는 경우 있음
also fun
또한 재미
its previous efforts and so this link on that as a function of everything and
이전 노력과 모두의 함수로 그에 따라서이 링크
it's very kind of uniform and kinda like a gene that you just 233 called too much
균일 한의 매우 친절 그리고 좀 유전자처럼 그냥 233을 너무 많이 불리는 그
in mexico india recurrent and that's a maybe that's just the answer my simplest
멕시코에서 인도 재발하고는 어쩌면 그건 내 간단한 그냥 대답의의
thing so somebody so if you'd like to use spatial temporal commercial networks
일이 이렇게 누군가 당신은 공간 시간 상용 네트워크를 사용하고 싶습니다 그래서 만약
and your projects and your very excited because your videos the first thing to
당신의 프로젝트와 매우 흥분 때문에 동영상에 제일 먼저에
do is stop and you should think about whether or not you really need to
중지하면됩니다 그리고 당신은 당신이 정말로 필요 여부에 대해 생각해야
process locomotion or global motion or emotion is really important your
프로세스 운동 또는 전역 움직임이나 감정이 정말 중요합니다 당신의
classification task if you really think motion is important to you then think
분류 작업 당신이 정말로 운동이 그 다음 생각에 중요하다고 생각하는 경우
about whether or not you need to model local motions are those are important
로컬 움직임이 그가 중요하다 모델링 할 필요가 있는지 여부에 대한
for all the global motion is very important
모든 전역 움직임을 위해 매우 중요하다
based on that you get a hint of what you should try about you always have to
당신은 항상에이에 대해 당신이 시도해야 당신이의 힌트를 얻을에 기반
compare that to a single from baseline I would say and then you should try using
내가 말을 기준으로 한 해당 비교 한 다음 사용하여 시도해야
optical flow because it seems that if you especially smaller amount of data it
광학 플로우는 것 때문에 그 경우 데이터의 당신이 특히 적은 양의 그것
actually is very important it's like a very nice signal tax lien code that and
실제로는 아주 좋은 신호 세금 선취 특권 코드처럼 매우 중요하다 및
explicitly specified that optical flow is a useful feature to look at and you
명시 적으로 광 흐름이 나와 보는 유용한 기능이라고 지정
can try this Dr you are seeing that work that afternoon just now but I think this
당신이 지금 막 오후 일을보고있는이 박사를 시도하지만이를 생각할 수
is too recent experimental so I'm actually not sure if I can fully
실험도 최근 그래서 나는 실제로 내가 충분히 할 수있는 경우에 확실하지 않다
endorses or if it works it seems like it's a very nice idea but it hasn't been
보증하거나 작동하는 경우가 아주 좋은 아이디어처럼 보인다하지만되지 않았습니다
proven yet and so that's that's kind of like the rock layout of happy process
아직 검증 그래서 그 행복 프로세스의 바위 레이아웃과 같은 종류의의의
videos in the field so I know if there is any questions because Justin is going
현장에서 동영상 그래서 나는 저스틴 가고 있기 때문에 질문이 있는지 알고
to come next
다음에 올
you are seeing this one hasn't been used for it all P thats good question I don't
이 일이 사용하지 않은보고있는 모든 P는 내가 안 좋은 질문 이잖아
think so I'm not super duper expert on LLP but I haven't seen this idea before
내가 LLP 슈퍼 괜찮아요 전문가가 아니에요하지만이 생각하기 전에 보지 못했지만 그렇게 생각
so i would i would guess that I haven't seen her I don't think so good
그래서 나는 내가 너무 좋아 생각하지 않는다 그녀를 보지 못했다 추측 할 것
in on a side with a million I would say that definitely something people would
만 가진 측에 나는 확실히 뭔가 사람들이 할 말을
want to do you don't see too many papers that do both of them just because people
당신은 단지 사람들 때문에 둘 다 할 너무 많은 논문을 볼 수 없습니다 싶은
like the kind of guy sleeping problems and tackle them maybe not jointly but
그리고 사람의 수면 문제의 종류와 같은 것은 어쩌면 그들을 해결되지 공동으로하지만,
certainly the company are trying to get something working in a real system you
확실히 회사는 실제 시스템에 뭔가 작업을 얻으려고 노력하는 당신
would do something like that but I don't think there's anything that you would do
그런 일을 할 것입니다하지만 난 당신이 할 것입니다 거기에 아무것도 생각하지 않습니다
you probably do this with the late fusion approach where you have a
당신은 아마 당신은이 말 융합 접근 방식으로이 작업을 수행
whatever works best on videos whatever works best on audio and then emerged out
오디오에서 가장 잘 작동하고 밖으로 나왔다 무엇이든 동영상에 가장 적합
somewhere later somehow but that's only something I can do and with contend with
어딘가 나중에 어떻게 든하지만 내가 할 수있는 유일한 뭔가하고와 함께 주장
the neural networks right very simple because you just have a player that's
신경망 권리 매우 간단 당신은 그냥 선수가 있기 때문에
looking at the output of both at some point and then you're classifying as a
어떤 점에서 둘의 출력을보고 다음은로 분류하고
function of both so we're going to surprise them and I guess we have to get
모두의 기능은 그래서 우리는 그들을 놀라게 할거야 그리고 나는 우리가 얻어야 할 것 같아요
here
이리
hopefully it works
희망 그것은 작동
ok so I guess we're gonna switch gears completely and entirely and talk about
확인 그래서 우리가 완전히 완전히 거 스위치 기어를하고있어 대한 이야기​​ 같아요
unsupervised learning so I'd like to make a little bit of a contrast here
자율 학습은 그래서 여기에 대비 약간을하고 싶습니다
that first we're gonna talk about some sort of basic definitions on
먼저 우리의 기본 정의 어떤 종류의에 대한 거 얘기 야
unsupervised learning and we're going to talk about two different sort of ways
자율 학습은 우리는 방법에 대한 두 개의 서로 다른 종류의 이야기거야
that unsupervised learning has recently been attacked by deporting people so in
그 자율 학습은 최근에 그래서 사람을 추방에 의해 공격되었다
particular we gonna talk about auto encoders and then this idea of
특히 우리는 자동차 인코더와의이 아이디어에 대한 이야기​​를 거
adversarial networks and I guess I need my clicker right so pretty much
적대적 네트워크와 내가 바로 그렇게 꽤 많이 내 리모콘이 필요 같아요
everything we've seen in this class so far is supervised learning so the basic
우리가 지금까지이 클래스에서 본 적이 모든 기본 그래서지도 학습이다
setup behind pretty much all supervised learning problems is that we assume that
거의 모든지도 학습 문제 뒤에 설치는 우리가 가정이다
our dataset has sort of each data point has sort of two distinct parts we have
우리의 데이터 세트는 각 데이터 포인트의 종류는 두 가지 부품의 종류를 가지고있다 우리는이
our data access and then we have some label or output why that we want to have
우리의 데이터 액세스 한 다음 우리는 우리가 원하는 것을 왜 어떤 라벨 또는 출력이
produced from that from that input and our whole goal in supervised learning is
해당 입력에서 해당로부터 생산 및 감독 학습에서 우리의 전체 목표는
to learn some function that takes in our input tax and then produces this output
우리의 매입 세액에 걸리는 일부 기능을 학습하고이 출력을 생성합니다
or label why and if you really think about it pretty much almost everything
또는 당신이 정말로 그것을 거의 거의 모든 것에 대해 생각하는 이유와 경우 레이블
we've seen in this class is some instances of this supervised learning
우리가이 클래스에서 보았던 것은이지도 학습의 일부 예입니다
set up so something like image classification acts as an image and then
다음 이미지로 이미지를 분류 행위 같은 뭔가를 설정하고
why is a label for something like object detection access an image and then why
물체 검출과 같은의 라벨은 왜 이미지 및 액세스 이유
is maybe a set of objects in the image that you won't find why could be a
가 될 수 이유를 찾을 수 없습니다 이미지에서 개체의 집합 어쩌면이다
caption and then we look at capture name could be a video and now why it could be
이 될 수 왜 우리가 캡처 이름을보고 캡션 후 이제 비디오하고 수
either a label or a caption or pretty much anything anything so I just want to
레이블 또는 캡션 또는 거의 아무것도 아무것도 중 하나는 그래서 난 그냥 원하는
make the point that supervised learning is this very very very powerful powerful
학습 감독 점이 강력한이 매우 매우 매우 강력하게
and generic framework that encompass encompasses everything we've done in the
그리고 포함 일반적인 프레임 워크는 우리가에서 수행 한 모든 것을 포함
class so far and the other point is that supervised learning actually make system
지금까지 클래스와 다른 점은지도 학습은 실제로 시스템을 만드는 것입니다
that works systems that work really well in practice and is very useful for
즉, 실제로는 정말 잘 작동 시스템을 작동하고 매우 유용합니다
practical applications
실제 응용
unsupervised learning i think is a little bit more of an open research
내가 생각 자율 학습은 개방 연구의 조금 더
question at this point in time so it's really cool I think it's really
정말 멋진, 그래서이 시점에서 질문 나는 정말 생각
important for solving a guy in general but at this point it's maybe a little
일반적으로 사람을 해결하기위한 중요하지만이 시점에서 그것은 아마도 약간의
bit more of a research focus to type of area it's also a little bit less
영역의 유형에 대한 연구의 초점 이상의 비트는 또한 약간의 작은
well-defined so it's an unsupervised learning we generally assume that we
우리가 일반적으로 우리 가정 자율 학습, 그래서 잘 정의
have just data we only have pacs we don't have any why
우리는 PACS를 그냥 데이터 우리는 어떤 이유가없는 한
and the goal of unsupervised learning is to do something with that data acts and
및 자율 학습의 목표는 데이터의 역할과 일을하는 것입니다
the something that we're trying to do really depends on the problem so some so
우리가 정말로하려는 일이 너무 일부 그래서 문제에 따라 달라집니다
in general we hope that we can discover some type of latent structure in the
일반적으로 우리는 우리가에 잠재 구조의 몇 가지 유형을 발견 할 수 있기를 바랍니다
data acts without explicitly knowing anything about the labels so some
데이터는 명시 적으로 어떤 레이블에 대해 아무것도 모른 채 역할
classical examples that you might have seen in previous machine learning
당신이 이전의 기계 학습에서 볼 수도 고전적인 예
classes would be things like clustering so something like a means we're just a
클래스는 그래서 수단과 같은 우리가 그냥있어 클러스터링 같은 것들이 될 것이다
bunch of points and we discover structure by classifying them into
점의 무리 우리는로를 구분하여 구조를 발견
clusters some other classical examples of unsupervised learning would be
클러스터는 자율 학습의 다른 고전적인 예는 것
something like principal component analysis where X is just at this point
X이 시점에서 그냥 주성분 분석과 같은
of data and we want to discover some low-dimensional representation of that
데이터의 우리는 그 중 일부 저 차원 표현을 발견 할
input data so unsupervised learning is this really is sort of cool area but a
입력 데이터 그래서 자율 학습이 정말 종류의 멋진 지역 만입니다
little bit more problems specific and a little bit less well defined in
조금 더 문제가 구체적이고 약간은 덜 잘 정의
supervised learning so two things that to architecture is in particular that
아키텍처로 특정되어 있으므로 두 가지를 학습 감독
people in deep learning have done for unsupervised learning these ideas as
깊은 학습 사람들은이 아이디어로 자율 학습에 대해 수행 한
this idea of an audio encoder will talk about sort of traditional Ottoman
오디오 인코더의이 아이디어는 전통적인 오스만의 종류에 대해 이야기합니다
quarters that have a very very long history will also talk about variational
또한 변분에 대해 이야기하는 아주 아주 오랜 역사를 가지고 분기
auto encoders which are this sort of news cool Asian twist on them will also
뉴스의이 종류이다 자동 인코더는 것입니다 그들에 아시아 트위스트를 냉각
talk about some generative adversarial networks that actually this really nice
실제로 일부 생식 적대적 네트워크에 대해이 정말 좋은 이야기
idea but let you generate images and model sample from natural images so the
생각하지만 당신은 너무 자연스러운 이미지의 이미지와 모델 샘플을 생성 할 수
idea with an audio encoder is is pretty simple
인 오디오 인코더와 아이디어는 매우 간단하다
we have our input sacks which is some data and we're gonna pass this input
우리는 일부 데이터이며, 우리는이 입력 거 패스 야하는 우리의 입력 자루가
data through some kind of encoding network to produce some features some
인코딩 네트워크의 어떤 종류를 통해 데이터에서 일부 기능을 생산하는 일부
latent features so this you could think this stage you could think up a little
이 단계를 생각할 수이 있도록 잠재 기능을 사용하면 약간을 생각할 수
bit like a learnable principal component analysis we're going to take our input
우리는 우리의 입력을거야 학습 가능 주요 구성 요소 분석과 같은 비트
data and then converted into some other feature representation so those many
다음 데이터 그래서 그 많은 다른 기능 표현으로 변환
times these access will be images like these are 10 images shown here so this
이 10 이미지 때문에이 여기에 표시됩니다 같은 시간은 이러한 액세스는 이미지가 될 것입니다
this encoder network could be something very complicated so for something like
이 인코더 네트워크는 같은 뭔가를 이렇게 아주 복잡한 일을 할 수
PCA it's just a simple linear transform but in general this might be a fully
PCA는 그냥 간단한 선형 변환이야 그러나 일반적으로이 완벽하게 될 수 있습니다
connected network originally sort of maybe five or 10 years ago this
연결된 네트워크 원래 종류의 아마 다섯 10 년 전
often a single they're fully connected to network with sigmoid units now it's
종종 하나의 그들은 그것의 현재 시그 모이 단위로 네트워크에 완벽하게 연결되어
often a deep deep network with trailer units and this could also be something
트레일러 단위 종종 깊은 깊은 네트워크와이 또한 뭔가 될 수 있습니다
like a convolutional not work right so we also have this idea that Z
길쌈 바로 그렇게 작동하지처럼 우리는이 생각이있는 Z
the features that we are that we learn are usually smaller in size than acts so
그래서 역할을보다 우리가 배울 수있는 기능의 크기는 일반적으로 작은
we won't need to be some kind of useful features about the data acts so we we
데이터 그래서 우리는 우리의 역할에 대해 우리는 유용한 기능의 일종 할 필요가 없습니다
don't want the network to just transform the net transport the data into some
그냥 몇 가지로 인터넷 전송에게 데이터를 변환하기 위해 네트워크를 원하지 않는다
useless representation we want to force that actually crush the data down and
쓸모없는 표현은 우리가 실제로 데이터를 분쇄 강제로 원하는
summarize it statistics and some useful way that could hopefully be useful
통계 및 희망 도움이 될 수있는 몇 가지 유용한 방법을 요약
person downstream processing but the problem is that we don't really have any
사람 다운 스트림 처리하지만 문제는 우리가 정말 어떤을하지 않아도됩니다
explicit labels to use for this downstream processing so instead we need
명시적인 레이블 그래서 대신에 우리가 필요로하는이 다운 스트림 처리를 위해 사용하는
to invent some kind of a surrogate ask that we can use using just just the data
대리의 어떤 종류를 발명 우리가 단지 데이터를 사용하여 사용할 수있는 요청
itself so the circuit asked that we often use for auto encoders is this idea
자체 회로는 우리가 자주 자동 인코더에 사용하는 요구 있도록이 좋습니다
of reconstruction so since we don't have any wise to learn a mapping instead
재건의 우리는 매핑을 대신 배울 수있는 지혜가없는 사람, 그래서
we're just gonna try to reproduce the data acts from those features Z and
우리는 이러한 기능의 Z에서 데이터의 행위를 재현 단지 거 시도하고 있고
especially if those features are smaller in size than hopefully that'll force the
이러한 기능은보다 크기가 작은 특히 희망 그것은 강제합니다
network to act to summarize
네트워크 요약하는 역할을합니다
to summarize the useful statistics of the input data and hopefully discover
입력 데이터의 유용한 통계 요약 희망 발견 할
some useful features that could be one useful for reconstruction but more
재건하지만 더 유용 하나가 될 수있는 몇 가지 유용한 기능
generally might be those features might be useful for some other tasks if we
일반적으로 이러한 기능은 다른 작업에 유용 할 수 있습니다 수 있습니다 우리의 경우
later get some supervised data so again this decoder network could be pretty
나중에 어떤 감독 데이터를 얻을 그래서 다시이 디코더 네트워크는 꽤 될 수있다
complicated when auto in quarters so first came about
숙소에서 자동 그래서 처음에 대한 왔을 때 복잡
oftentimes these were just simply either a simple linear network or a small
종종 이들은 단지 간단한 선형 네트워크 또는 작은 하나 있었다
signal network but now they can be deeply networks and often times these
네트워크 신호하지만 지금은 깊이 네트워크와 종종이 될 수 있습니다
will be up convolutional is a good time so it's Mason small inflatable slides so
길쌈까지 될 것입니다 것은 너무 메이슨 작은 풍선 슬라이드, 그래서 좋은 시간입니다
oftentimes this decoder nowadays will be one of these up convolutional networks
자주이 디코더는 현재이 최대 길쌈 네트워크 중 하나가 될 것입니다
that takes your features that are again are smaller in size than your input data
즉, 다시 수 있습니다 귀하의 입력 데이터보다 크기가 작은 당신의 기능을한다
and kind of blows it back up in size to reproduce your original data and I'd
및 종류의 원본 데이터를 재생 내가 좋겠하는 크기까지 다시 불면
like to make the point that these things are actually pretty easy to train so the
이러한 일들이 실제로 그렇게 훈련을 아주 쉽게 있다는 점을 확인하려면
right here is a quick example that I just cooked up in torch so this is for
바로 여기가 그래서 난 그냥 토치에서 요리하는 간단한 예제입니다
larry
래리
code which is accomplished all that work for their decoder which is up
최대 그들의 디코더에 대한 모든 작업을 수행되는 코드
convolutional network and you can see that it's actually learns to reconstruct
컨볼 루션 네트워크 당신은 실제로 재구성 배운다있어 것을 알 수 있습니다
the data pretty well another thing that you sometimes see is that these encoder
가끔 볼 꽤 잘 다른 것은 데이터가 이러한 인코더이다
and decoder networks will sometimes share weights with just sort of as a
및 디코더 네트워크는 때로는 종류의 같은과 가중치를 공유합니다
regularization strategy and with this intuition that these are opposite
정규화 전략과 이러한 반대 있음이 직감으로
operations so maybe I might make sense to try to use the same waits for both so
작업은 그래서 어쩌면 난 둘 정도 같은 대기를 사용하려고하는 것은 의미가 있습니다
just as a concrete example if you're in if you think about a fully connected
당신이 완전히 연결에 대해 생각하면 그냥 구체적인 예를 들어 당신은에 있다면
network then maybe your input data has some dimension d
네트워크는 아마도 사용자의 입력 데이터의 일부 치수 D를 갖는
and then you're late and data the will have some smaller dimension H and if
그리고 당신은 늦게와 데이터는 약간 작은 치수 H를 가지고있는 경우 것
this encoder was just a fully connected network then the weights will just be
이 인코더는 가중치 그냥 될 것 그냥 완전히 연결 네트워크했다
this matrix of Dubai age and now when we want to do the decoding and try to
이 두바이 시대의 매트릭스와 지금 우리가 디코딩을하고하려고 할 때
reconstruct the original data than that
보다 원래의 데이터를 재구성
mapping back from each back to D so we can just reuse the same weights in these
다시 D에 각각의 뒷면에서 매핑 그래서 우리는 단지이 동일한 가중치를 재사용 할 수 있습니다
two areas we just take a transpose of a matrix so when we're training this thing
우리가이 일을 훈련 할 때 두 가지 영역 우리는 너무 행렬의 전치을
we need some kind of a loss function that we can use to compare a
우리는 비교하는 데 사용할 수있는 손실 함수의 어떤 필요
reconstructed data with our original data and then once and oftentimes will c
재구성 된 우리의 원래 데이터와 데이터를 다음 번 자주 것 다
L to a simple like hell to Euclidean loss to train this thing so once we've
우리가하면, 그래서 유클리드 손실 지옥 같은 간단한에 L이 일을 훈련합니다
chosen our internet work and once we've chosen rd quarter network and function
우리의 인터넷 작업을 선택하고 우리는 번째 분기 네트워크와 기능을 선택한 후
then we can train this thing just like any other normal neural network where we
우리는 다른 보통의 신경망처럼이 일을 훈련 할 수있는 우리
get some data we pass it through to encode it we passed through decoded the
디코딩을 통해 우리를 통해 전달할 일부 데이터를 인코딩에 도착 우리는 통과
computer law sweetback propagate and everything's good so once we train this
컴퓨터 법률 sweetback의 전파 모든 것이 우리가이 훈련 그래서 일단 좋은
thing then oftentimes will take this decoder network that we spent so much
물건은 자주 우리가 너무 많은 지출이 디코더 네트워크를 취할 것
time learning and I'll just throw it away which seems kinda weird but the
시간 학습과 난 그냥 좀 이상한 보인다 그것을 멀리 던질거야하지만,
reason is that reconstruction on its own is not such a useful task so instead we
이유는 자체적으로 재구성하므로 대신 같은 유용한 작업 없다는 것이다 우리
want to apply these networks to some kind of actually useful task which is
입니다 실제로 유용한 작업의 일종으로 이러한 네트워크를 적용 할
probably a supervised learning task so here to set up is that we've learned
아마 설정하기 때문에 여기에 감독 학습 과제는 우리가 배운 것입니다
this encoder network which hopefully from all this unsupervised data has
희망이 모든 자율 데이터로부터이이 엔코더 네트워크
emerged to has learned to compress the data and extract some useful features
데이터를 압축하고 몇 가지 유용한 기능을 추출하기 위해 배운 등장
and then we're going to use this encoder network to initialize part of a larger
그리고, 우리는 더 큰 부분을 초기화하기 위해 인코더 네트워크를 사용하는거야
supervised work and now if we actually do have access to maybe some smaller
우리가 실제로 어쩌면 몇 가지 작은에 액세스 할 경우 지금 감독 업무와
data set
데이터 세트
that have some labels then hopefully this most of the work here could have
다음 희망이 작업 대부분이 여기에있는 수있는 몇 가지 레이블이
been done by this unsupervised training at the beginning and then we can just
처음에이 자율 훈련을 수행 한 후 우리는 할 수있는 한
use that to initialize this this bigger network and then fine tune the whole
전체이 더 큰 네트워크를 한 후 미세 조정이를 초기화하는 것을 사용
thing with hopefully a very small amount of supervised data so this is kind of a
관리 대상 데이터의 희망을 아주 소량 것은 그래서 이것은의 종류
dream of one of the dreams of unsupervised feature learning that you
자율 기능 학습의 꿈 중 하나의 꿈 당신을
have this really really large datasets with no labels you can just go on Google
그냥 구글에 갈 수없는 레이블이 정말 큰 데이터 세트를
and download images forever and it's really easy to get a lot of images
영원히 이미지를 다운로드하고 이미지를 많이 얻을 정말 쉽습니다
the problem is the labels are expensive to collect so you'd want some system
문제는 레이블 그래서 당신은 어떤 시스템을 싶어 수집하는 비용이있다
that could take advantage of both a large huge amount of unsupervised data
즉 자율 많은 데이터 엄청난 양 모두를 이용할 수도
and also just a small amount of supervised data so automakers are at
또한 자동차 제조에서 감독 데이터의 단지 작은 양 그래서
least one thing that has been proposed that has this night property but in
이 밤 속성 만에이 제안되고있다 적어도 한 가지
practice I think it tends not to work too well which is a little bit
내가 조금 인 너무 잘 작동하지 않는 경향이 생각하는 연습
unfortunate because it's such a beautiful idea another thing that I
이 아름다운 그런 생각이 다른 것 때문에 불행한 그 I
should point out almost as a side note that if you go back and read the
거의 다시 가서 읽으면하는 보조 노트로 지적해야
literature on these things from the mid to thousands in the last 10 years than
지난 10 년 이상에서 수천 중반부터이 일에 문학
people have this funny thing called increase their wives pre-training that
사람들은 자신의 아내가 미리 훈련 증가이라는 재미있는 것은이 그
they used for training auto encoders and share the idea was that at the time in
그들은 자동 인코더 훈련에 사용하고 생각했다 공유 그 시간에
2006 training very deep networks was was challenging and if you you can find
매우 깊은 네트워크가 있었다 2,006 훈련은 도전이고 당신이 경우 당신은 찾을 수 있습니다
quotes and papers like this that say that even when you have maybe 45 hidden
당신이 가지고있는 경우에도 아마 45 숨겨진 말과 같이 인용 및 논문
layers it was extremely challenging per pupil in those days to train networks so
층이 있도록 네트워크를 훈련 당시 학생 당 극단적으로 도전했다
it to get around that problem with a instead had this paradigm where they
대신 곳 패러다임을 가진과 그 문제를 해결 얻을들이
would try to train just one letter at a time and they use this this thing but i
한 번에 하나의 편지를 양성하려고 그들은이이 일을 사용하지만 난 것
dont wanna get too much into called the Restricted Boltzmann machine which is a
싶어이있는 제한된 볼츠만 기계 호출에 너무 많이 얻을 해달라고
typographical model and they would use these restricted Boltzmann Machines the
인쇄상의 모델 그리고 그들은 이러한 제한 볼츠만 기계를 사용하는 것
kind of trainees to these little there's one at a time so first we will have our
한 번에 하나씩 거기에이 작은에 연수생의 종류 그래서 우리는 먼저해야합니다 우리의
input image may be sized up of size W one and this would be maybe something
입력 이미지 크기 W 하나의 최대 크기가 될 수 있으며, 이것은 아마 뭔가 될 것
like PCA or some other kind of pics transform and then we would hopefully
PCA 또는 사진의 다른 종류의 같은 변환 한 후 우리는 희망 것
learn using a restricted Boltzmann machine some kind of relationship
제한된 볼츠만 기계에게 관계의 어떤 종류를 사용하여 배울 수
between those first their features and some higher level features when once we
그 첫 번째 자신의 기능과 몇 가지 높은 수준의 기능 사이에 때 한 번
once we learned this layer within reason
우리는 이유에서이 층을 알게되면
and learn another restricted Boltzmann machine on top of those features
그 기능의 상단에 다른 제한 볼츠만 기계 학습
connecting it to the next level features so by using this type of approach it let
이러한 유형의 접근법을 사용하여 다음 레벨의 기능으로되도록 접속하면하자
them train just one layer at a time in this sort of greedy way and that let
그 욕심 방법 및 그하자 이런 종류의에서 한 번에 하나의 층을 훈련
them hopefully find a really good initialization for this larger network
그들에게 희망이 더 큰 네트워크에 대한 정말 좋은 초기화를 찾을 수
so after this greedy pre-training stage they would stick the whole thing
그래서이 욕심 사전 교육 단계 이후 그들은 전체를 스틱 것
together into this giant audio encoder and then fine tune the audio encoder
함께이 거대한 오디오 인코더 다음 미세 조정 오디오 인코더로
jointly so nowadays we don't really need to do this with things like ray Liu and
공동 요즘, 그래서 우리가 정말 선 리우와 같은 것들로이 작업을 수행 할 필요가 없습니다
proper initialization and bash normalization and slightly fancier
적절한 초기화 및 bash는 정상화 약간 애호가
fancier optimizers this type of thing is not really necessary anymore so as an
일의이 유형은 그래서으로 더 이상 정말 필요하지 않습니다 애호가 최적화
example on the previous slide we saw this for Larry convolutional
이전 슬라이드의 예를 우리는 래리 길쌈이를 보았다
deconvolution audio encoder that I trained on ceasefire and this is just
내가 휴전에 훈련이 그냥 디컨 볼 루션 오디오 인코더
trying to do
일을하려고
using all these modern neural network techniques you don't have to mess around
모든 현대적인 신경망 기술을 사용하면 주위에 엉망이 없습니다
with US Airways training so this is not something that really gets done anymore
미국 항공 훈련 그래서 이것은 정말 더 이상 수행되는 것이 아닙니다
but I thought we should at least mentioned it since you're probably
하지만 난 당신이 아마에 있기 때문에 우리는 적어도 언급해야한다고 생각
encounter this idea if you read back in the literature about these things so the
당신이 그래서 이런 것들에 대한 문헌에서 다시 읽으면이 아이디어를 발생
basic idea or an auto in quarters is I think pretty simple it's this beautiful
기본적인 아이디어 또는 분기 자동차는 나는이 아름답다 아주 간단 생각한다
idea where we can just use a lot of unsupervised data to hopefully learn
우리가 희망을 배울 자율 많은 양의 데이터를 사용할 수있는 아이디어
some nice features unfortunately that doesn't work but that's ok but there's
몇 가지 좋은 기능은 불행하게도 그 작동하지 않습니다하지만 괜찮아요하지만 거기에
maybe some other nice type of task we would want to do with unsupervised data
아마 작업의 다른 좋은 유형 우리는 자율 데이터로 할 것
question first
질문 첫 번째
yesterday the question is what what's going on here right so this is this is
어제 질문은 여기에서 일어나고 것은 바로 그래서 이것은 이것이 무엇이다
this is maybe you could think about a three-layer neural network so our input
이것은 어쩌면 당신이 우리의 입력 때문에 세 계층 신경 네트워크에 대해 생각할 수있다
is gonna be the same as the output so we're just hoping that this is a neural
거 것은 그래서 우리는 단지이 신경 것을 바라고 출력과 동일
network that will learn the identity function but that's a really and in
네트워크 식별 기능을 배울하지만 정말하고에있어 것
order to learn the identity function we have some loss function at the end
우리 끝에 일부 손실 함수를 갖는 항등 함수 학습하기 위해서
something like an adult who lost that is encouraging our to our input and output
그 손실 성인과 같은 우리의 입력과 출력에 우리를 격려한다
to be the same and learning identity function is probably really easy thing
같은 학습 식별 기능으로 아마 정말 쉬운 일입니다
to do but instead we're going to force the network to not take the easy route
수행하는 대신 우리는 쉽게 경로를하지하기 위해 네트워크를 강제하는거야
and instead hopefully rather than just regurgitating the data and learning the
대신 희망이 아니라 단지 데이터를 토하는 및 학습보다
identity function in the easy way instead we're gonna bottlenecks
쉬운 방법으로 식별 기능을 대신 우린 병목 현상이야
representation through this hidden layer in the middle so then it's gonna learn
중간에이 숨겨진 레이어를 통해 표현은 그래서 다음거야 배울 수 있어요
the identity function but in the middle of the network is gonna have to squeeze
신원 기능하지만, 네트워크의 중간에 거이다가 집어 넣은해야
down and summarize and compress the data and hopefully that that compression will
아래 데이터를 요약하고 압축하고 잘하면 그 그 압축 것
give rise to features that are useful for other tasks as that may be a little
그 조금이 될 수 있으므로 다른 작업에 유용한 기능을 야기 할
bit more care ok questioned the claim was that PCA is just the answer for this
좀 더 배려 확인은 주장 PCA이 단지 해답이었다 의문을 제기
problem so it's true that PCA is optimal in certain senses if you're only allowed
문제는 그래서 만 허용하는 경우 PCA 특정 감각에 최적 인 것은 사실이다
to do one where a wonder if your income and your decoder are just a single
경이는 소득 및 디코더가 단지 하나의 경우 어디 하나를 수행합니다
linear transform then indeed PCA of optimal in some sense but if you're in
당신이 있다면 어떤 의미에서 최적의 참 다음 PCA 변환하지만, 선형
quarter and decoder are potentially larger more complicated functions that
분기 및 디코더는 잠재적으로 더 큰 더 복잡한 함수이다 그
are more maybe multi-layer neural networks then then maybe PCA is no
더 어쩌면 다층 신경망은 어쩌면 PCA가 더있다 없다
longer the right solution another point to make is that PCA is only optimal in
더 이상 다른 점은 수있는 권리 솔루션은 PCA는 단지 최적이다
certain senses
특정 감각
particularly talking about LG reconstruction but in practice we don't
특히 LG의 재건에 대해 이야기하지만 실제로 우리는하지 않습니다
actually care about reconstruction we're just hoping that this thing will learn
실제로 우리가이 일을 배울 것으로 기대하고 재건에 관심
useful features for other tasks so in practice and will see this a bit later
다른 작업에 유용한 기능 연습 때문에이 조금 이상을 볼 것이다
that people don't always use out to anymore because I'll to is maybe not
나는 아마되는 것이기 때문에 사람들은 항상 더 이상에게 사용하지 않는 것이
quite the right loss for actually features yeah
사실에 매우 적합한 손실 그래 특징
the army on larry is this is is this kind of generative model of the data of
이것은이다 래리의 군대의 데이터의 생성 적 모델의이 종류이다
data where you imagine that you have sort of two sequences of bets and you
당신이 내기 당신의 종류의 두 시퀀스가​​ 상상 데이터
want to do this
이 작업을 수행 할 수
generative modeling of the of the two things so then you need to get into
두 가지의 생식 모델링 그래서 당신은 들어갈 필요
quite a lot of reasons that this text to figure out exactly what a loss function
이 텍스트는 정확히 손실 기능을 파악하는 것이 이유 중 꽤 많은
is but it ends up being something like what likelihood of the data with these
하지만, 이들로 데이터를 어​​떤 우도 추천되는 것을 끝낸다
latent state that you don't observe and that's actually a cool idea that we will
당신이 관찰되지 않고 그것이 우리가 의지하는 것이 실제로 멋진 아이디어 잠복 상태
sort of revisit in the variational audio encoder so one of the one of the
일종의의 하나 하나 있도록 변분 오디오 인코더에 다시 방문
problems with this traditional audio encoder is that it's hoping to learn
전통적인 오디오 인코더 문제는 배우를 바라고 있다는 것입니다
features that's that's a cool thing but there's this other thing that we would
즉 그 멋진 일이의 기능을하지만 다른 일이 우리가 것입니다
like to not just learned features but also be able to generate new data a cool
에 같은 단지 기능을 습득뿐만 아니라 멋진 새로운 데이터를 생성 할 수 없습니다
task that we could potentially learned from unsupervised data is that hopefully
우리는 잠재적으로 자율 데이터에서 배운 수있는 작업은 희망입니다
our model could slurp and a bunch of images and after it does that it sort of
우리 후루룩 소리 내며 먹기 수있는 모델과 이미지의 무리 그것은 일종의 그 것을 수행 한 후
learns what natural images look like and then after its learn this distribution
자연 이미지의 모습과이 메일 내용은 다음 후 무엇을 배운다
then it could hopefully spit out sort of fake images that look like the original
그것은 희망 원래의 모습 가짜 이미지의 종류를 뱉어 수
images but are fake and this is maybe not address a task which is directly
이미지하지만 가짜 이것은 어쩌면 바로 작업을 처리하지 않습니다
applicable to things like classification but it seems like an important thing for
분류 같은 것들에 적용 할 수 있지만, 중요한 일처럼 보인다
a guy that humans are pretty good at looking at data and summarizing it and
인간이 데이터를 찾고 그것을 요​​약에서 꽤 좋은 사람과
getting the idea of what it looks like so hopefully if our models could also do
그렇게 희망을 갖고 우리의 모델도 할 수 있다면 어떻게 생겼는지의 아이디어를 얻기
this sort of task then hopefully they'll have learned some some useful
작업의 이런 종류는 잘하면 그들은 몇 가지 유용한 배운 것
summarization or some useful statistics of the data so the variation audio
요약이나 데이터의 일부 유용한 통계 변동 오디오 그래서
encoder is this kind of neat twist on the original order that lets us
인코더는 우리가 할 수있는 원래 순서에 깔끔한 트위스트의이 종류이다
hopefully actually generate novel images from our learns data so here we need to
희망 실제로 그래서 여기에 우리 배운다 데이터에서 새로운 이미지를 생성 우리는 필요
dive into a little bit of patience that this tax so this is something that we
인내의 약간에 뛰어 것을이 세금은 그래서 이것은 뭔가가 우리
haven't really talked about at all in this class anymore but up to this point
정말이 시점에 더 이상하지만까지이 클래스에 대해 전혀 이야기하지 않은
but there's this whole other side of machine learning that doesn't do near
하지만 근처하지 않는 기계 학습의이 모든 다른 측면이있다
networks and deep learning but things really hard about probability
확률에 대한 정말 열심히 네트워크와 깊은 학습하지만 일
distributions and how bility distributions can fit together to
분포 및 부 합성 분포는 서로에 들어갈 수있는 방법
generate data sets and then reason probabilistically about your data and
데이터 세트 다음 이유를 확률 적 데이터와에 대해 생성
this type of paradigm is really nice because it lets you sort of State
그것은 당신에게 국가의 종류 수 있기 때문에 패러다임의이 유형은 정말 좋은
explicit probabilistic
명시 적 확률
assumptions about how you think your data was generated and then given those
당신이 당신의 데이터를 어​​떻게 생각하는지에 대한 가정이 생성 한 후 그 주어졌다
probabilistic assumptions you try to figure model to the data that follows
확률 적 가정은 다음과 데이터에 모델을 파악하려고
your assumptions so what the variation alarming quarter we're assuming this
당신의 가정은 그래서 변화 놀라운 분기 우리는이 가정을하는지
this particular type of method by which our data was generated so we assume that
우리가 가정 있도록 방법이 특정 유형은하는 우리의 데이터가 생성 된
we've barely exists out there in the world some prior distribution which is
우리는 거의 세계가 몇 가지 사전 분포를 존재했습니다
generating these latent States Z and we've been we assume some conditional
이러한 잠재 미국 Z를 생성하고 우리는 우리는 몇 가지 조건 가정했습니다
distribution that once we have the leading states we can generate samples
일단 우리는 우리가 샘플을 최고의 상태를 생성 할 수있는 유통
from some other distribution to generate the data so the variation audio encoder
다른 분포 변동 오디오 인코더 따라서 데이터를 생성하도록
it really imagine that our data was generated by this pretty simple process
정말 우리의 데이터가이 꽤 간단한 과정에 의해 생성 된 상상
that first we sample from some prior distribution to get some to get raz B
먼저 우리는 몇 가지가 RAZ의 B를 얻기 위해 얻기 위해 몇 가지 사전 분포에서 샘플링 있음
sample from this conditional to get our acts so the intuition is that acts as
직관이 그 역할을하므로이 조건에서 샘플은 우리의 행위를 얻을 수
something like an image and Z maybe summarizes some useful stuff about that
이미지와 Z 같은 아마 그것에 대해 몇 가지 유용한 물건을 요약
image so if these were see far images then maybe that lay in state she could
이 훨씬 이미지를 볼 수 있었다, 그래서 만약 이미지 어쩌면 상태에 누워 그 그녀는 수
be something like the class of the image whether it's a frog or a deer or cat and
이 개구리 나 사슴 또는 고양이 여부 이미지의 클래스 같은 것을하고
also might contain variables about how that cat is oriented or what color it is
또한 고양이가 지향하거나 어떤 색 방법에 대한 변수를 포함 할 수 있습니다
or something like that
또는 그런 일
so this is kind of a nice sort of having a pretty simple some pretty simple idea
그래서 이것은 매우 간단 꽤 간단한 아이디어를 가진의 좋은 종류의 종류
but makes a lot of sense for how you might imagine image images to be
하지만 당신이되고 이미지의 이미지를 상상하는 방법에 대한 많은 이해
generated so the problem now is that we want to ask to meet these parameters
문제 때문에 발생 지금 우리는 이러한 매개 변수를 충족 물어보고 싶은 것입니다
data of both the prior and the conditional without actually having
종래 실제로 않고 조건부 모두 데이터
access to these latest dates and see and that's that's the that's a challenging
그 도전의 이러한 최신 날짜에 대한 액세스를 참조하고는이의의
problem so to make a simple we're gonna do something that you see a lot in
문제는 그래서 우리는거야 간단한 당신이에서 많이 볼 일을 만들려면
Bayesian statistics and I'll just assume that the priors got a shampoo that's
베이지안 통계 및 난 그냥 전과가있어 샴푸를 가지고 있다고 가정합니다
easy to handle and the conditional be a will also be shown but it's gonna be a
취급이 용이하고, 조건은 또한 표시됩니다 수 있지만 될거야 될 것
little bit fancier so we'll assume that it's a Gaussian with diagonal mean and
조금 애호가 그래서 우리는 대각선 평균과 가진 가우스 있다고 가정합니다
unit with sorry diagonal covariance and some mean but instead we're just gonna
대신 죄송 대각 공분산 어떤 의미하지만,과 단위 우리는 단지거야
put but the way that we're going to get those is we're going to compute them
넣어하지만 우리는 사람들을 얻기 위하여려고하고있는 방법은 우리가 그들을 계산하는거야입니다
with a neural network so it suppose that we had the latest agency for some piece
신경 네트워크 그래서 우리가 어떤 부분에 대한 최신 의지를 가지고 있다고 가정
of data that we assume that that late instead
데이터 우리는 그 말 대신한다고 가정
will go into some decoder network which could be some big complicated neural
몇 가지 큰 복잡한 신경이 될 수있는 몇 가지 디코더 네트워크로 이동합니다
network and now that neural network is gonna spit out two things it's gonna
네트워크와 지금 신경 네트워크는 거이 거의 두 가지를 뱉어입니다
spit out the meaning of the data it's gonna spit out the meaning of the data
데이터의 의미를 뱉어는거야 데이터의 의미를 뱉어 것
acts and also the the the variance of the data acts so you should think that
행위 또한 데이터의 상기 분산은 그래서 당신이 생각해야 작용
this looks very much like the top half of a normal audio encoder that we have
이것은 우리가 보통 오디오 인코더의 위쪽 절반 같은​​ 아주 많이 보인다
this link state we have some known that that's operating on the latest eight but
우리가 어떤 그건 것으로 알려져있는이 링크 상태 최신 팔에서 작동하지만,
now instead of just directly spitting out the data instead it's spitting out
지금 대신 직접 데이터를 침 대신에 그것을 밖으로 뱉어 것
the mean of the data and the variance of the data but other than that this looks
데이터의 평균이 보이는 것보다 데이터의 분산되지만 다른
very much like the decoder of the normal audio encoder so this this decoder
매우 일반적인 오디오 인코더의 디코더 등이이 디코더 그래서
network sort of thinking back to the normal audio encoder might be a simple
일반 오디오 인코더 다시 생각의 네트워크 종류는 간단한 수 있습니다
fully connected thing or it might be this very big powerful deconvolution
완전히 연결된 것은 아니면이 매우 큰 강력한 디컨 볼 루션 수 있습니다
network and both of those are pretty common so now the problem is that by
네트워크 이들 모두 문제가있다 의한 지금 매우 일반적인
baseball if given the prior and given the conditional basil tells us the
사전을 부여하고 조건 바질가 주어진다면 야구는 우리가 알
posterior that given so if we want to actually use this model we need to be
우리가 실제로이 모델을 사용하려면 우리가 할 필요가 있도록 주어진 것을 후부
able to estimate the latent state from the input data and the way that we
상기 입력 데이터와 상기 방식에서 잠복 상태를 추정 할 수있는 것을 우리
estimate the leading state from the input data is by writing down this
입력 데이터에서 최고의 상태를 추정하면이를 작성하는 것입니다
posterior distribution which is the probability of the latest easy given are
쉽게 주어진 최신의 확률 사후 분포
observed data and using payroll we can easily flip this around and write it in
관측 데이터 및 급여를 사용하여 우리는 쉽게 주위에이 플립과 그것을 쓸 수 있습니다
terms of our prior oversee and in terms of our conditional Givenchy and so we
우리의 전 감독과 우리의 조건 지방의 관점에서 등 조건 우리
can use by Israel to actually put this thing around and write it in terms of
이스라엘 사용할 수 있습니다 실제로 주위에이 일을두고 측면에서 그것을 쓰기
these three things so after we look at these roles we can break down these
우리가 이러한 역할을보고 난 후에 우리는 이것들을 분해 할 수 있도록 이러한 세 가지
three terms and we can see that the conditional we just use our decoder
세 가지 용어와 조건은 우리가 우리의 디코더를 사용하는 것이 우리는 볼 수 있습니다
network and we easily have access to that and this prior again we have access
네트워크와 우리는 쉽게 그에 대한 액세스 권한이 이전에 다시 우리가 접근
to the prior to be assumed that you negotiate so that's easy to handle but
사전은 당신이 협상 것으로 가정 할에 그래서 다루기 쉽게하지만,
this denominator this probability of acts it turns out if you if you work out
당신은 당신이 운동하는 경우 경우이 분모의 역할이 확률​​은 밝혀
the math and write it out this ends up being this giant intractable in a row
수학이 행에이 거대한 난치성 인 끝을 쓰는
over the entire leading state space so that's completely intractable there's no
그 완전히 다루기 힘든, 그래서 전체 선도적 인 상태 공간을 통해 더 없다
way you could ever porn that in a girl and even approximating it would be a
방법은 당신이 할 수 이제까지 포르노도 근사 여자와 그것이 될 것이라고
giant disaster so instead we will not even trying to evaluate that in a girl
거대한 재난 그래서 대신에 우리는 심지어 여자에 그 평가하려고하지 않습니다
instead we're going to introduce some encoder network that will try to
대신 우리는하려고 몇 가지 인코더 네트워크를 소개하는거야
directly before
직접 전
in print stuff for us so this encoder network is going to take in a data point
우리의 인쇄 재료에 때문에이 엔코더 네트워크는 데이터 포인트에 걸릴 것입니다
and it's going to spit out a distribution over the meeting state
그리고 회의의 상태에 걸쳐 분포를 뱉어 것
space so again this looks very much looking back at the original audio
공간은 그래서 다시는 매우 원래 오디오를 다시 찾고 보인다
encoder from a few slides ago this looks very much the same as sort of the bottom
몇 슬라이드에서 인코더 전이 매우 하단의 종류와 같은 모양
half of a traditional audio encoder where we're taking in data and now
우리가 지금 데이터에 복용하는 기존의 오디오 인코더의 절반
instead of directly spitting out the latest eight we're gonna spit out a mean
대신 직접 최신 팔을 침으로 우리는거야 평균을 뱉어하고
and variance of the leading state and again this quarter network might be
및 주요 국가의 분산 다시 이번 분기 네트워크가 될 수 있습니다
something might be somewhat controversial network or maybe some deep
뭔가 다소 논란의 네트워크 또는 어쩌면 약간의 깊은 수 있습니다
convolutional network so sort of the intuition is that this encounter network
컨볼 루션 네트워크는 그래​​서 직관의 종류입니다이 만남 네트워크
will be the separate totally different destroying function but we're going to
별도의 완전히 다른 파괴하는 기능이있을 것입니다하지만 우리는 거 야
try to train it in a way that it approximates this posterior distribution
그것은 이러한 사후 분포에 근사하는 방식으로 훈련 시도
that we don't actually have access to and so when we probably pieces together
우리는 실제로 그렇게 할 때 우리는 아마 조각을 함께에 액세스하지 않는 것이
then then we can set up a stitch this all together and get give rise to this
그 다음 우리는 이것에 상승을 줄이 모두 함께 스티치를 설정하고 얻을 수 있습니다
variation audio encoder so once we put these things together then we have this
변화는 오디오 인코더 번, 그래서 우리는 우리가이 다음 함께 이러한 것들을 넣어
input data point X we're gonna pass it through our encoder network and the
입력 데이터 포인트의 X 우리 것 우리의 인코더 네트워크와 통해거야 패스를
encoder network will spit out a distribution over the leading states
인코더 네트워크는 최고의 상태에 대한 분포를 뱉어
once we have this this distribution over the latest dates you can imagine you
우리는 최신 날짜 이상이이 메일을 일단 당신이 상상할 수
could imagine sampling from that distribution to get some some highest
그 분포에서 샘플링을 상상할 수있는 것은 얻기 위해 일부 일부 최고
let me state of high probability for that input than once we have been once
우리가 한 번왔다하면보다 그 입력을 나에게 높은 확률의 상태를 보자
we have some concrete example of a latent state then we can pass it through
우리는 잠재 상태의 몇 가지 구체적인 예를 우리는 그것을 통과 할 수
this decoder network which will spread out the probability of which should then
이 디코더 네트워크 확률을 밖으로 확산되는있는 다음해야
sped out the probability of the data again and then once we have this
우리가이 있으면 다시 다음 데이터의 확률을 가속화
distribution over the data we could sample from it to actually get something
우리는 그것에서 맛볼 수있는 데이터에 대한 분포는 실제로 뭔가를 얻을 수
that hopefully looks like the original data point so this this ends up looking
그 희망이보고 끝이 때문에 원본 데이터 점처럼 보이는
very much like a normal audio encoder where we're taking our input data we're
우리는 우리가있어 우리의 입력 데이터를 복용하고 일반 오디오 인코더와 같은 매우
running it through this encoder to get some latent state or passing into this
일부 잠재 상태를 얻기 위해이 엔코더를 통해 실행하거나에 전달
decoder totally reconstruct the original data and when you go about training this
디코더는 완전히 원래의 데이터를 재구성하고이 훈련에 대해 갈 때
thing it's actually trained in a very similar method as normal audio encoder
물건은 실제로 일반 오디오 인코더와 같은 매우 유사한 방법에서 훈련이야
we have this for past and this backward pass the only difference is in the loss
우리는 과거이 있고이 이전 버전과의 유일한 차이점은 손실에 전달
function so at the top we have this reconstruction loss rather than being
기능 상단에 우리는이 재건 손실이 아닌 것을 있도록
displayed by sl2 instead we want this distribution to be close to the true
(SL2)에 의해 표시 대신에 우리는이 분포가 실제에 근접 할
input data and we also have this lost term coming in the middle that we want
입력 데이터와 우리는이를 우리가 원하는 중간에 나오는 용어를 잃었다
this generated distribution over the Layton States hopefully be very similar
레이튼 미국을 통해이 발생 분포는 희망 매우 유사
to our stated prior distribution that we wrote down at the very beginning so once
우리의 명시된 사전 분포에 우리는 매우 그래서 한 번 시작 부분에 아래로 썼다
you put these pieces together you can just trying this thing like a normal
당신은 그냥 보통처럼이 일을 시도 할 수 있습니다 함께 이러한 조각을 넣어
audio encoder with normal forward forward forward pass and backward pass
앞으로 전진 패스 정상 앞으로 오디오 인코더 및 후방 패스
the only difference is where you put the loss and how you interpret the loss so
만약 손실을 넣고 어떻게 그렇게 손실 해석 여기서 유일한 차이점은
any any questions about the setup it's kind of a when we went through a kind of
우리의 종류를 통해 갈 때 어떤 설정에 대한 질문 그것은 종류입니다
ass yeah question is why do you choose a diagonal covariance and answers cuz it's
그것의 사촌 엉덩이 네 질문은 왜 대각 공분산과 답변을 선택합니까된다
really easy to work with theirs but actually people have tried I think
정말 쉬운 그들의 작업을 할 수 있지만, 실제로 사람들은 내가 생각하는 시도
slightly fancier things too but that's something you can play around with ok so
약간 너무 일을 애호가하지만 당신이 너무 좋아 함께 놀러 수있는 일이다
once we've actually trained this once we've actually trained this kind of
우리가 실제로 한 번이 훈련을하고 나면 우리는 실제로 이러한 종류의 훈련을했습니다
variational audio encoder we can actually use it to generate new data
변분 오디오 인코더 우리는 실제적으로 새로운 데이터를 생성하는 데 사용할 수
that looks kind of like original dataset so here
즉, 그래서 여기 종류의 원본 데이터 셋처럼 보이는
the idea is that remember we wrote down this prior that might be a you negotiate
아이디어는 기억하고 있음을 우리는이 이전 될 수있는 당신이 협상 적어된다
or maybe something a little bit fancier but at any rate this prior is something
아니면 뭔가 조금 애호가하지만 어떤 속도로이 사전은 뭔가
some distribution that we can easily sample from so you negotiate it's very
당신이 아주의 협상 그래서 우리는 쉽게에서 맛볼 수있는 유통
easy to draw random samples from that distribution so to generate new data
그 분포에서 무작위 샘플을 그리 쉽게 그래서 새로운 데이터를 생성하는
will start by just sort of following this data this data generation process
그저이 데이터이 데이터 생성 과정에 따라 시작됩니다
that we had imagined data so first we'll sample from our from our prior
먼저 우리는 우리의 사전에서 우리의에서 샘플링됩니다, 그래서 우리는 데이터를 상상했던 것을
distribution over the lake in states and then we'll pass it through our decoder
국가에있는 호수에 분포하고 우리는 우리의 디코더를 통해 전달됩니다
network that we have learned during training and this decoder network will
우리는 훈련 기간 동안 배운 네트워크와이 디코더 네트워크는 것
now spit out a distribution override and appoints in the turn in in terms of both
지금 모두의 측면에서에서 차례로 분배 무시하고 임명을 뱉어
I mean and covariance and once we have a mean and covariance this is just a
내 말과 공분산 우리는 평균과 공분산이되면이 단지입니다
diagonal gosh we can easily sample from this thing again to generate some data
대각선 세상에는 우리가 쉽게 몇 가지 데이터를 생성하기 위해 다시이 일에서보실 수 있습니다
point so now 11 you train this thing then another thing you can do is sort of
당신이 할 수있는 다른 일이 종류의 당신이이 일을 훈련 그래서 지금 11 포인트
can out the latent space and I'm at and rather than sampling from a latent
잠재 공간에서 할 수있는 난에 오히려 잠재에서 샘플링보다 해요
distribution instead you just densely sample of allegiance from the latest
최신에서 충성의 분포 대신에 단지 밀집 샘플
base to kind of get an idea of what type of structure structure the network had
베이스 종류의 네트워크가 가진 구조 구조의 유형의 아이디어를 얻을 수 있습니다
learned so this is doing exactly that on this dataset so here we we trained this
우리는 우리가이 훈련 그래서 이것은 그래서 여기에이 데이터 집합에 정확히하고있다 배웠다
variation audio encoder with where is the latest eight is just a
최신 여덟 곳으로 변화 오디오 인코더 단지입니다
two-dimensional thing and now we can actually scan out this late in space we
일이 차원 이제 우리는 실제로 공간에서이 말을 스캔 할 수 있습니다 우리
can explore densely this two-dimensional late in space and for each point in the
늦은 공간 및 각 포인트에 대한 밀도가 이러한 2 차원 탐색 할
latent space passes through the decoder and use it to generate some image you
잠상 공간 디코더 통과 일부 화상을 생성하도록 사용하면
can see that it's actually discovered this beautiful structure it's that sort
실제로는 그런 종류의 아름다운 구조를 발견 있다고 볼 수 있습니다
of smoothly interpolates between the different digit classes so I'll be up
I가있을 것이다, 그래서의 원활 다른 자리 클래스 사이에 보간
here at the left you see six is the kind of morph into zeros as you go down you
여기에서 당신을 아래로 가서 당신이 여섯 제로로 모프의 종류 참조 왼쪽
see six is that turned into seven into BB nines and Southern's the aids are
볼 여섯 것으로는 BB의 화려로 칠로 설정되어 남부의 에이즈은
hanging out in the middle somewhere in the ones are down here so this latent
이 잠재 그래서 여기에 아래로 사람 어딘가에 중간에 매달려
space actually learned this beautiful disentanglement of the data in this very
공간은 실제로 아주에있는 데이터의이 아름다운 풀림을 배웠다
nice unsupervised way we can also turn this thing on our faces dataset and it's
좋은 자율 방식으로 우리는 또한 우리의 얼굴 데이터 세트에이 일을 설정할 수 있습니다 그것은이다
the same sort of story where we're just training this two-dimensional variation
우리가이 2 차원의 변화를 훈련하고 이야기의 같은 종류의
audio encoder and then once we train it we densely sampled from that late in
오디오 인코더 다음 우리가 훈련을하면 우리는 밀도에서 늦은에서 샘플링
space to try to see what he has learned western
공간은 그가 서 배운 것을보고 시도
yeah so the question is whether people ever try to force the least specifically
그래 그래서 문제는 사람들이 지금 가장 구체적를 강제로 시도 여부
variables to have some some some exact meaning and yeah there has been some
변수는 일부 일부 일부 정확한 의미를하고 그래 몇 가지가있다
follow-up work that does exactly that there is a paper called deep inverse
후속 정확하게 수행 작업을 깊은 역이라는 종이가 있음
graphics networks from MIT that has that does exactly this setup where they try
그들이 시도 정확하게이 설정을 수행하는 것이이 MIT에서 그래픽 네트워크
to force where they want to learn sort of a renderer in as a neural network so
의 신경망으로 그들이 렌더러의 종류를 학습 할 위치를 강제로 그렇게
they want to learn to like render 3d images of things they want to force some
그들은 일부를 강제 할 것들의 3D 이미지를 렌더링 좋아하는 배우고 싶어요
of the latent space some of the variables in the latent space to
잠재 공간에서 변수의 일부 잠재 공간
corresponds to the the 3d angles of the object and maybe the class and the
물체의 3 차원 각도와 아마 클래스와에 대응
repose of the object and the rest of them it led to learn from whatever it
물체와 그 나머지의 휴식은 무엇이든 배울지도 그
wants and that she has some cool experiments were now they can do exactly
원하고 그녀가 가지고있는 멋진 실험은 지금은 정확히 할 수 있었다
as you said and by setting those those specific values the latent variables
당신이 말한으로 그 그 특정 값을 잠재 변수를 설정하여
that can render and actually rotate the object and those are those are pretty
그 렌더링 실제로 객체를 회전 것들이다 그 꽤 있습니다 할 수 있습니다
cool but that's that's that's a lot of fancier than these spaces but these
멋진하지만 그건 그건있어 그 다음에 공백 그러나이보다 애호가의 많은입니다
faces are still pretty cool you can see it sort of interpolating between
얼굴은 여전히​​ 당신이 종류의 사이에 보간 볼 수 있습니다 꽤 멋진
different phases in this very nice way and I think that there's actually a very
다른이 아주 좋은 방법 단계와 나는 실제로 아주가 있다고 생각
nice motivation here and one of the reasons we pick a diagonal tension is
좋은 동기 부여 여기 이유 중 하나 우리는 대각선 긴장이 선택
that that has the probabilistic interpretation of having independent but
그 독립을 갖는의 확률 적 해석을 가지고 있지만,
that the very different variables in our living space
우리의 생활 공간에서 매우 다른 변수
actually should be independent so I think that helps to explain why there
실제로 독립적 그래서 나는 그 이유가 설명하는 데 도움이 생각해야
actually is this very nice separation between the accys when you end up
당신이 끝날 때 실제로 accys 사이의 아주 좋은 분리입니다
sampling from the lead in space is due to this probabilistic independence
공간에있는지도에서 샘플링이 확률 적 독립성 때문이다
assumption embedded in a prior so this idea prior to this very powerful and
에 포함 된 가정 이전 그래서이 아이디어 이전이 매우 강력와
lets you sort of big those types of things directly into a model so I I
당신이 종류의 큰 일 이러한 유형의 직접 모델 그래서 II에 있습니다
wrote down a bunch of math and I don't think we really have time to go through
수학의 무리를 쓴 나는 우리가 정말 통과 시간이 생각하지 않습니다
it but the idea is that sort of classically when you're training
그것은하지만 아이디어는 훈련있어 고전 때의 일종이다
generative models there's this thing called maximum likelihood where you want
생식 모델 당신이 원하는 최대 우도라는이 일있다
to maximize the likelihood of your data under the model and then pick the model
모델에 따라 데이터의 우도를 최대화하고 모델을 선택하는
where that makes your data most likely but it turns out that if you just try to
즉, 데이터가 가장 가능성이 있습니다하지만 당신은 그냥하려고하면 밝혀 곳
run maximum-likelihood using a normal using this generative process that we
최대 우도 생식이 공정을 이용하여 통상의 사용을 실행하는 것이 우리
had imagined for the very issues older than you run into this giant you end up
당신은 당신이 결국이 거대한로 실행보다 나이가 바로 그 문제에 대해 상상했던
needing to marginalize this joint distribution which becomes this giant
이 거인이되는이 공동 분배를 소외 필요
intractable in a girl over the entire meeting state space that's not something
뭔가 아니다 전체 회의 상태 공간을 통해 소녀에서 다루기 힘든
that we can do
우리가 할 수있는
so instead the various audio encoder encoder does this thing called a
그래서 대신에 다양한 오디오 인코더 인코더는이 일이라고 않는
variational inference which is a pretty cool idea and the math is here in case
변분은 정말 멋진 생각이다 추론하는 그리고 수학은 경우에 여기에있다
you want to go through it but the idea is that instead of maximizing along
당신은 그것을 통해 가고 싶어하지만 아이디어는 대신에 따라 극대화하는 것입니다
probability of the data work on a cleverly insert this extra content and
A의 데이터 일 가능성이 영리이 추가 컨텐츠를 삽입하고
break it up into these two different terms so we're right this is an exact
우리는 바로이 정확한 것입니다있어, 그래서이 두 가지 다른 용어로 그것을 깰
equivalents that you can maybe work there on your own but this log
당신은 아마 자신 만이 로그에이 작업 할 수 등가물
likelihood we can write in terms of this term that we call an elbow and this
가능성 우리는 우리가 팔꿈치를 호출이 용어의 관점이에서 쓸 수 있습니다
other term which is a Cal divergence between two distributions and we know
이 분포하고 우리는 아는 사이 칼의 차이가 다른 용어
that killed two virgins is always zero so we know that killed two virgins
두 처녀를 죽인 그래서 우리는이 처녀를 죽인 것을 알고 항상 0이다
between distributions is non-zero so we know that this term has to be non-zero
분배 사이에서 우리가이 용어는 비 - 제로이어야한다는 것을 알 비 제로
which means that this this elbow term actually is a lower bound on the log
이는이이 팔꿈치 용어는 실제로 로그에 결합 된 낮다는 것을 의미한다
likelihood of our data and notice that in the process of writing down this
우리의 데이터의 가능성이 아래로 작성하는 과정에서 그 통지
elbow we introduce this additional parameter feed that we can interpret as
팔꿈치 우리는 우리가 같이 해석 할 수있는이 추가 매개 변수 피드를 소개합니다
the parameters of this this encoder network that is sort of approximating
일종의 근사되어이이 엔코더 네트워크의 매개 변수
this hard posterior distribution so now instead of trying to directly maximize
그래서 지금 대신 직접 극대화하는 노력이 하드 사후 분포
the log likelihood of our data instead will try to maximize this very issue
우리의 데이터의 로그 가능성이 대신 바로이 문제를 극대화하기 위해 노력할 것입니다
lower bound of the data and because the elbow is as a lower bound of the log
데이터 바인딩 및 팔꿈치 같은 저급 때문에 로그 하한
likelihood then maximizing the elbow will also have the effect of raising up
다음 팔꿈치 최대화 가능성도까지 상승시키는 효과를 가질 것이다
the log likelihood and stuff and these these two terms of the elbow actually of
로그 가능성과 물건과 실제의 팔꿈치이이 두 용어
this beautiful interpretation that this one at the at the front is the
전면의에서이 하나가 있음이 아름다운 해석
expectation over the Layton States be over the latent state space of the
레이튼 상태에 대한 기대의 잠재 상태 공간 이상이어야
probability of X given the latent state space so you think about that that's
당신이이 있다고 생각하므로 X의 확률은 잠재 상태 공간을 제공
actually a data reconstruction term that's saying that if we averaged over
말하는 실제로 데이터 재구성 기간 우리가 이상 평균 경우 그
all possible eighteen states that we should end up with something that is
우리가 무언가와 끝까지해야 가능한 모든 십팔 상태
similar to our original data and this is at this this other term is actually a
우리의 원래의 데이터와 유사한이이 다른 용어는 실제로는 이것이다
regularization term this is the Cal divergence between are approximate
정규화 기간이 대략 사이의 칼 발산하다
posterior and between the prior so this is a regularization of trying to force
후부 및 이전 사이에 그래서 이것은 강제로 시도의 정규화입니다
those two things together so impact this this this first term you can approximate
당신이 대략 수있는 그 두 가지가 함께 그래서이이 첫 번째 임기에 영향을 미칠
with something called the approximate by sampling using this trick in the paper
뭔가 논문에서이 트릭을 사용하여 샘​​플링하여 대략적인 호출
that I won't get into and this other term again because everything is going
모든 것이 예정되어 있기 때문에 나는 다시이 다른 용어로 얻을하지 않습니다
on here you can just about the skilled emergence explicitly
여기에 당신이 단지 숙련 출현에 대해 가능한 명시 적으로
so I think this is the most map every slide in the class so that's that's kind
그래서 나는이 그 그 종류의의 때문에 대부분의 클래스에있는 모든 슬라이드를지도 생각
of fun but actually it's so but it's actually scary but it's actually just
재미 있지만, 실제로는 그래서하지만 실제로 무서운하지만 그것은 단지 사실이다
exactly just this one quarter idea we have a reconstruction and then you have
정확히 바로이 사분의 아이디어 우리는 재건이 후, 당신은
this penalty penalizing to you to go backwards the prior to any any questions
당신에게 처벌이 페널티는 질문에 뒤로 이전 이동
on the various quarters as that in general the idea of an audio encoder is
다양한 분기 해당 일반적으로 오디오 인코더의 생각대로
that we want to force a network to try to reconstruct our data and hopefully
우리는 희망을 갖고 우리의 데이터를 재구성하려고하는 네트워크를 강제하려는
this will learn sort of useful representations of the data for Trisha
이 트리샤에 대한 데이터의 종류의 유용한 표현을 배울 것
lot of encoders this is used for Peter learning but once we move to variation
우리는 변화에 이동하면 인코더의 많은이 피터 학습에 사용되지만,
in quarters we make this thing patients so we can actually generate samples that
우리가 실제로 샘플을 생성 할 수 있도록 분기에 우리는이 일 환자를 확인하는
are similar to our data so then this idea of generating samples from my data
그럼 내 데이터에서 샘플을 생성하는이 아이디어 우리의 데이터와 유사
is really cool and everyone loves looking at these kinds of pictures so
정말 멋진이며, 모든 사람이 사진의 이러한 종류의 너무보고 사랑
there's another idea that maybe can we generate really cool samples without all
어쩌면 우리 모두가없이 정말 멋진 예제를 생성 할 수있는 또 다른 생각이있다
this scary Bayesian math and it turns out that there's this idea called a
이 무서운 베이지안 수학 그리고 그것은이라는 생각이 있다고 밝혀
generative adversarial network that is a sort of different idea a different twist
다른 생각 다른 트위스트의 일종이다 생식 적대적인 네트워크
that lets you still generate samples that look like your data but sort of a
즉, 여전히 데이터 만의 일종처럼 보이는 샘플을 생성 할 수 있습니다
little bit more explicitly without having to worry about divergences
좀 더 명시 적으로 이견에 대해 걱정할 필요없이
umpires and this sort of stuff
심판과 물건을 이런 종류의
the idea is that we're gonna have a generator not work that well first we're
아이디어는 우리가거야 발전기가 처음 우리가 있다는 것을 잘 작동하지 않은 것입니다
gonna start with some random noise that probably has drawn from you negotiate or
당신이 협상에서거야 아마 받고있다 일부 랜덤 노이즈로 시작하거나
something like that and then we're going to have a generator network and this
그 다음 우리는 발전기 네트워크를 가지고거야,이 같은
generator network actually looks very much like the decoder in the variational
발전기 네트워크는 실제로 매우 많은 변분의 디코더처럼 보이는
audio encoder or like the second half of a normal audio encoder in that we're
오디오 인코더 또는 우리가 야한다는 점에서 일반 오디오 인코더 년 하반기와 같은
taking this random noise and we're gonna spend out an image that is going to be
이 랜덤 노이즈를 복용하고 우리가 될 것입니다 이미지를 보낼거야
some fake not real image that we're just generating using this train network then
우리는 단지 다음이 열차 네트워크를 사용하여 발생하는 일부 가짜하지 실제 이미지
we're also going to hook up a discriminator network that is going to
우리는 또한에가는 판별 네트워크를 연결하는거야
look at this fake image and try to decide whether it's whether or not that
이 가짜 이미지를보고이 있는지 여부를 그 여부를 결정하려고
generated image is real or fake
생성 된 이미지는 실제 또는 가짜
so this is this so the second network is just doing this binary classification
그래서 이것은이 때문에 제 2 네트워크는 단지이 이진 분류를하고있다
task where it receives an input and it just needs to say whether or not it's
작업은 입력을 수신하는 경우 그리고 그것은 단지 그것의 여부를 말할 필요
it's true or it's whether or not it's real image or not that's just sort of a
그것은 사실이나 그것이 실제 이미지인지 아닌지의 여부 그건 그냥 일종의이야
classification task that you can hook up like anything else
당신이 다른 것처럼 연결할 수 있습니다 분류 작업
so then we can train this thing called all jointly altogether
그래서 우리는 공동으로 완전히 모든 호출이 일을 훈련 할 수있다
where r generator network will receive many batches of random noise and I'll
R 발전기 네트워크 랜덤 노이즈의 여러 배치를받을 것이다 어디거야
spit out and it'll take images and our discriminator network will receive many
뱉어과 이미지를 할게요 우리 판별 네트워크는 많은을 받게됩니다
batches of partially these images and partially real images from a dataset and
데이터 집합에서 부분적으로 이러한 이미지의 배치를 부분적으로 실제 이미지와
it will have to do it will try to make this classification task to say which
그것은 대답이 분류 작업을 만들기 위해 노력할 것입니다해야 할 것이다
are real and which are fake and so this is sort of now another way that we can
진짜와 가짜있는 등이 또 다른 방법은 지금 종류의 우리가 할 수있다
hook up this kind of supervised learning problem ish without any real data so we
실제 데이터없이지도 학습 문제 틱의이 종류를 연결 우리 때문에
hope this thing up and we train the hoping jointly so we can look at some
까지이 일을 희망 그리고 우리는 우리가 어떤 볼 수 공동으로 기대 훈련
examples from the original general adversarial networks paper and so these
그래서이 원래 일반적으로 적대적 네트워크 종이에서 예
are fake images that are generated by the network announced you can see that
당신이 볼 수있는 발표 네트워크에 의해 생성 된 가짜 이미지입니다
it's done a very good job of actually generating fake tits they look like real
그것은 그들이 진짜처럼 실제로 발생 가짜 가슴의 아주 좋은 일을 있어요
digits and here I'm here this this middle column is showing actually the
숫자와 여기를 내가 여기이 가운데 열있어 실제로 보여주고있다
nearest neighbor in the training set of those digits to hopefully let you know
그 자리의 트레이닝 세트의 가장 가까운 이웃이 희망을 알려합니다
that it doesn't just memorize the training set so for example this too has
예를 들어이 너무있다, 그래서 그냥 훈련 집합을 기억하지 않습니다
a little dot and then this guy doesn't have a dot so it's not just memorizing
그냥 기억하지 그래서 약간의 점과 다음이 사람은 도트가 없습니다
training data and it also does a pretty good job of recognizing pace
데이터를 교육하고 또한 인식 속도의 꽤 좋은 일을
generating faces so but you know as people who worked in machine learning
생성 그렇게 얼굴 그러나 당신은 기계 학습에서 일한 사람으로 알고
known these these digits and paste data sets tend to be pretty easy to generate
알려진 이러한 숫자와 붙여 넣기 데이터 세트를 생성 아주 쉽게하는 경향이
samples from and when we apply this this task to see far than RJR samples don't
에서 샘플 우리는 RJR 샘플을하지 않는 것보다 훨씬 볼이이 작업을 적용 할 때
quite look as nice and clean so here it's clearly got some idea about CPR
아주 보면 친절하고 깨끗한 그래서 여기 명확하게 CPR에 대한 몇 가지 아이디어를 가지고
data worth making blue stock and green stuff but they don't really look like
블루 stock와 녹색 물건을하지만 그들은 정말처럼 보이지 않는 가치 데이터
real objects so that's that's a problem so it's a follow-up work actually tried
실제로 시도 후속 작업 그래서 그 해당 그래서 실제 객체는 문제입니다
some follow-up work on generative adversarial networks has tried to make
생식 적대적 네트워크에 대한 몇 가지 후속 작업을 만들기 위해 노력하고 있습니다
these architectures bigger and more powerful so hopefully be able to
더 크고 더 강력한 이러한 아키텍처는 그렇게 희망 할 수있을
generate better samples on these more complex datasets so one idea is this
하나의 생각이 그래서이 더 복잡한 데이터 세트에 더 좋은 샘플을 생성
idea is multiscale processing so rather than generating the image all at once
아이디어는 다중 스케일 처리 때문에보다 한꺼번에 영상을 생성
we're actually gonna generate our image at multiple scales in this way so first
우리는 실제로 그렇게 먼저이 방법으로 여러 규모에서 우리의 이미지를 생성거야
we're gonna happen generator that feeds in bed receives noise and then generates
우리는 침대 후 발생 소음을 수신하고 피드 생성기 일어날거야
a low resolution and then we'll up sample that nora skyy and apply a second
낮은 해상도와 우리는 위로 그 노라의 SKYY 샘플 및 제를 적용합니다
generator
발전기
ur that receives a new batch of random noise and compute some Delta on top of
위에 일부 델타 랜덤 잡음의 새로운 배치를 수신하고, 계산 UR
the low res image then what up sample that again and repeat the process
낮은 고해상도 이미지를 다시 무슨 샘플과 과정을 반복
several times until we've actually finally generated are generated our
우리가 실제로 마지막으로 생성 할 때까지 여러 번 생성되는 우리의
final result so this is again a very similar ideas the previous as the
최종 결과는 그래서 이것은 다시로 이전 매우 비슷한 생각입니다
original gender diverse area network or just generating at multiple scales
원래 성별 다양한 영역 네트워크하거나 여러 규모에서 발생
simultaneously and the training here is a little bit more complex you actually a
동시에 여기에 훈련은 실제로 당신이 조금 더 복잡하다
discriminator at each scale and that hopefully hopefully there's something so
각 규모의 판별과 그 희망을 희망 그래서 뭔가있다
when we look at the train samples from this guy actually a lot better so here
우리는 그래서 여기에 훨씬 더 실제로이 사람에서 기차 샘플을 볼 때
are actually trained a separate model per class on C 510 so here they've
실제로 그래서 여기에 C (510)에 클래스마다 별도의 모델을 훈련 그들은했습니다
trained this adversarial network on just one just planes from CPR and you can see
CPR까지 한 단지 비행기에이 적대적 네트워크를 훈련하고 볼 수 있습니다
that they're starting to look like real planes so that's that's getting
그들은 그 그게 점점 그래서 실제 비행기처럼 보이기 시작하고 있다는
somewhere
어딘가에
these look almost like real quarters and these may be looked kinda like real
이 거의 실제 분기처럼 보이는 이들은 진짜처럼 좀보고 할 수있다
birds so in in the following year people actually threw away this multiscale idea
조류에서의 있도록 다음 해 사람들은 실제로 멀리이 다중 스케일 아이디어를 던져
and just used a simple are better more principled continent so here is the idea
단지 간단한 그래서 여기에 아이디어가 더 나은 더 원칙 대륙이다 사용
is forget about this multi skilled staff and just use use batch norm don't use
이 멀티 숙련 된 직원에 대해 잊고 그냥 사용하지 않는 사용 배치 표준을 사용한다
fully connected layers sort of all these architectural constraints that we've had
우리가 가진 한 모든 건축 제약 완전히 연결 레이어 정렬
become practice practice and last couple years just use those and turns out that
가 연습 연습과 지난 몇 년은 사람들을 사용하고 밝혀
your adversary in that span work really well so here they're generator is this
그 범위 작업에 대적 정말 잘 여기 그래서 그들은 발생이 인 것
pretty pretty simple pretty simple pretty small convolutional network and
아주 아주 간단합니다 아주 간단합니다 아주 작은 길쌈 네트워크와
the discriminator is again just a simple network with nationalization and all
판별 다시 국유화하고 모든 그냥 간단한 네트워크입니다
these other bells and whistles and once you hook up this thing they get some
이러한 다른 종과 경적 당신이이 일을를 연결하면 그들은 몇 가지를 얻을 수
amazing samples in this paper so these are generated bedrooms from the network
이러한 네트워크에서 침실을 생성하므로 본 논문에서 놀라운 샘플
so these actually are pretty impressive results these look like real data almost
그래서이 실제로 꽤 인상적 결과 이​​들은 실제 데이터처럼 거의
so you can see that it's done a really good job of capturing
그래서 당신은 캡처 정말 좋은 일을 끝낼 것을 알 수 있습니다
really detailed structure about bedrooms like there's a bad there's a window
나쁜 거기에 같은 침실 정말 상세한 구조는 윈도우있다
there's a light switch so these are these are really amazing samples but it
이러한이 정말 놀라운 샘플하지만되도록 전등 스위치가있다 그것은
turns out that rather than just generating samples we can play the same
오히려 방금 생성 된 샘플보다 우리가 같은 재생할 수 있습니다 밝혀
trick as the very issue lot of encoder and actually try to exploit try to play
실제로 인코더의 매우 문제가 많은 등의 트릭과 재생하려고 악용을 시도
around
약
meeting space because this cuz these adversarial networks are receiving this
이 이러한 적대적 네트워크가이 받고있는 사촌 때문에 회의 공간
noise input and we can cleverly try to move around that noise and put it and
노이즈 입력하고 우리는 영리 소음 주위에 이동하려고하고 그것을 넣을 수 있습니다
try to change the type of things that these networks generate so one example
이러한 네트워크 그렇게 일례를 생성하는 것들의 형태를 변경하려고
that we can try is interpolating between bedrooms so here on the left hip so here
우리는 그래서 여기에 왼쪽 엉덩이에 그래서 여기에 침실 사이에 보간됩니다 시도 할 수 있음
the idea is that on the left for these images on the left hand side we've drawn
아이디어는 왼쪽에 이러한 이미지의 왼쪽에 우리가 그린 한 것입니다
a random point from our noise distribution and then use it to generate
생성하기 위해 사용 후 우리 잡음 분포로부터 무작위 포인트
an image and now on the right hand side we've done the same and we generate
이미지는 이제 오른쪽 우리는이를 수행 한 결과 우리가 생성
another random point from our noise distribution and use it to generate an
우리 잡음 분포에서 다른 임의의 지점과는를 생성하는 데 사용할
image so now these these two guys on the opposite sides are generated are sort of
양측이이 두 사람이 생성 해주기 때문에 이미지가 일종의 있습니다
two points on a line and I we want to interpolate in the lead in space between
우리는 공간에서 리드 사이에서 보간하고자하는 라인과 I의 두 점
those two lead actors and along that line we're gonna generate used the use
두 리드 배우와 그 라인을 따라 우리가 거​​의 사용을 사용 생성하고
the generator to generate images and hopefully this will interpolate between
발전기는 이미지를 생성하고 희망이 보간됩니다
the latest dates of those two guys and you can see that this is pretty crazy
최신 두 사람의 날짜와이 꽤 미친 것을 알 수있다
that these bedrooms are more fame sort of in a very nice smooth continuous way
이 객실은 아주 좋은 부드러운 연속 방법으로 더 많은 명성 종류의 것을
from one bedroom to another and if you one thing to point out is that this
침실에서 다른 당신이 한 가지 지적 할 경우이 있다는 것입니다
morning is actually happening in kind of a nice romantic way if you imagine what
당신이 상상할 경우 아침은 실제로 좋은 낭만적 인 방법의 종류에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지
this would look like and pixel space than it would just be kind of this
그냥이 어떤 종류의 것보다이 픽셀 공간과 같을 것이다
fading effect and it would not look very good at all but here you can see that
효과를 페이딩과 전혀 매우 좋아 보이지 않을 것이다 그러나 여기 당신이 볼 수 있습니다
actually the shapes of these things and colors are sort of continuously
실제로 이러한 것들의 모양과 색상의 지속적 종류입니다
deforming from one side to the other which is quite fun so another experiment
또 다른 실험 있도록 아주 재미있는 다른 한쪽에서 변형
they have in this paper is actually using vector math to play around the
그들은 실제로 주위에 재생 벡터 수학을 사용하고이 문서에있는
type of things that these networks generate so here the idea is that they
이러한 네트워크가 생성 가지의 유형은 그래서 여기에 아이디어는 그들이
generated a whole bunch of random samples from the noise distribution then
다음 노이즈 분포에서 무작위 샘플의 전체 무리를 생성
pushed them all through the generator to generate a whole bunch of samples and
샘플의 전체 무리를 생성하는 발전기를 통해 그들 모두를 밀어
then they as he using their own human intelligence they tried to make some
그들은 그가 자신의 인간의 지능을 사용하여 그들이 몇 가지를 만들려고
semantic judgments about what those random samples look like and then group
그 랜덤 샘플 그룹 다음과 같이 무엇에 대한 의미 론적 판단
them into a couple of meaningful semantic categories so here at this
이것 때문에 여기에 의미 론적 범주의 몇 가지로
would be three things that three images that were generated from the network
세 가지가 될 것이라고 네트워크에서 생성 된 세 가지 이미지
that all kind of look like a smiling woman and those are human provided
모든 종류의 웃는 여자처럼 그 제공 인간
labels
라벨
here in the middle are three samples from the network of a neutral women that
여기 중간에 중립 여성의 네트워크에서 3 개의 시료는 그
are that's not smiling and share on the rate is 300 free samples of a man that
그 미소 요금에 공유 아니에요되는 것은 사람의 300 무료 샘플입니다
is not smiling so each of these guys was produced from some latent state vector
그래서이 사람들의 각각의 미소되지는 일부 잠재 상태 벡터에서 생성 된
so we'll just average those lay in state vectors to compute this sort of average
그래서 우리는 평균 이런 종류의 계산하는 상태 벡터에서와 평신도 평균 다만 것
average rating state of smiling woman neutral women and neutral man now once
웃는 여자 중립 여성과 중성 남자의 평균 평가 상태 지금 한 번
we have this latent state vector we can do some vector math so we can take a
우리는 우리가 어떤 벡터 연산을 할 수있는이 잠복 상태 벡터 그래서 우리가 걸릴 수 있습니다
smiling woman subtract a neutral woman and at a neutral man so what what would
웃는 여자 중립 여자를 빼고 중성 남자 그래서 무엇을 어떻게 것
that give you so you hope that would give you a smiling man and this is what
당신이 당신에게 웃는 사람을 줄 것이라고 희망 있도록 제공하고이게 무슨입니다
it generates so this actually it does kinda look like a smiling man that's
그것은 일종의의 웃는 남자 생겼 그래서이 실제로 발생
that's pretty amazing we can do another experiment we can take a man with
즉, 우리가 사람을 걸릴 수 있습니다 우리는 또 다른 실험을 할 수있는 아주 놀라운
glasses and a man without glasses and a man with glasses subtract the man with
안경 및 안경없이 남자와 안경 사람과 사람을 빼기
glasses and add a woman with glasses with no glasses this this is confusing
이이 혼란 안경없이 안경 안경 여자를 추가
stuff so that and what was this what would this little equation give us a
물건이었다 그래서 어떤이이 작은 방정식은 우리에게 줄 것이다 무엇
look at that so that's that's pretty crazy so it def assault even though
즉 그하더라도 그것 때문에 데프 폭행 꽤 미친 그래서 그 봐
we're not sort of forcing an explicit prior on the sleeping space space these
우리는 일종의 강제하지 않는 잠자는 공간 공간에 명시 적으로 이전이
adversarial networks have somehow still managed to learn some really nice useful
적대적 네트워크는 어떻게 든 여전히 유용 정말 좋은 내용을 관리해야
representation there so i also very quickly I think there's a pretty cool
이 표현은 그래서도 매우 빠르게 난 정말 멋진 있다고 생각
paper that just came out a week or two ago that puts all of these ideas
이러한 아이디어를 모두두고 그 두 주 전에 나온 그냥 종이
together like we covered a lot of different ideas in this lecture and
우리는이 강의에서 다른 생각을 많이 덮여 함께 같은과
let's just stick them all together so first we're gonna take a variation on
그냥 그렇게 먼저 우리는거야 함께 모든 스틱에 변화를 보자
quarter as as our starting point and this will have sort of the normal its
이 분기는 통상의 정렬을 갖하고 시작점으로서의
allies loss from various audio encoder but we saw that these adversarial
동맹국의 다양한 오디오 인코더 손실 그러나 우리는 이러한 적대적인 것을보고
networks give really amazing samples so why don't we had an adversarial network
하지 우리는 적대적인 네트워크를 가지고 왜 네트워크는 그래​​서 정말 놀라운 샘플을 제공
to the variation autumn quarter so we do that so now in addition to having our
우리가 가진뿐만 아니라 지금 그렇게하도록 변화가 분기에 우리의
variation ottoman quarter we also have this this discriminator network that's
변화 발판 분기 우리는 또한의이이 판별 네트워크가
trying to tell the difference between the
사이의 차이를 말하려고
no data and between the samples from the variational audio encoder but that's not
자료 없음과 샘플 사이의 변분 오디오 인코더하지만 그건 아니에요
cool enough so why don't we also download Alex NAT and then pass these
멋진 충분한 왜 우리는 또한 알렉스 NAT를 다운로드하지 않는 한 다음이 통과
two images
두 개의 이미지
Alex net and extract Alex net features for both the original image and four are
알렉스 그물 원래의 이미지와 4 개의 모두 알렉스 순 특징을 추출
generated image and now in addition to having a similar pics loss and hair and
또한 비슷한 사진 손실과 머리를 가지고 지금 이미지를 생성
pulling the discriminator we're also hoping to generate samples that have
우리는 또한이 샘플을 생성하기를 바라고있는 판별을 당겨
similar Alex net features as measured by all too and once you stick all these
너무 모든 측정 및 모든 스틱 한 번와 유사한 알렉스 순 기능
things together hopefully you'll get some really beautiful samples right so
일이 함께 희망 당신은 바로 그래서 정말 아름다운 샘플을 얻을 것이다
here are the examples from the paper so these are paid just train the entire
여기 그래서이 단지 전체 훈련을 지불하고있는 용지의 예입니다
thing on image that so we should I think this is these are actually quite nice
그래서 우리는 난이 이러한 사실은 꽤 멋지다 생각해야한다는 이미지 일
samples and if you contrast this with the multiscale samples on CPR that we
샘플 및 심폐 소생술에 다중 스케일 샘플이 대조 경우 그 우리
saw before for those samples remember they were actually training a separate
그 샘플이 실제로 별도의 훈련 된 기억을 위해 이전에 본
model per class and see fire and these those beautiful bedroom samples that you
클래스 당 모델 볼 화재 및이 그 아름다운 침실 샘플 당신
saw was again
톱을 다시했다
training one model that's specific to bedrooms but here they actually trained
침실에 고유이다 그러나 여기에서 실제로 교육 훈련을 하나의 모델
one model on all of internet and still like these are real images but they're
인터넷의 모든에 아직도 이런 하나의 모델은 실제 이미지하지만 그들은이야
definitely getting towards real issue looking images so that's i think these
확실히 그 내가이 생각, 그래서 진짜 문제를 찾고 이미지를 향해 점점
are pretty cool I also think it's kind of fun to just take all these things and
나는 또한 생각 꽤 멋진 그냥 모든 일을 재미의 종류 그리고
stick them together and hopefully get some really nice samples thats I think
함께 스틱 잘하면 내가 생각하는 그게 정말 좋은 샘플을 얻을
that's pretty much all we have to say about unsupervised learning so if
그것은 거의 우리가 만약 그렇다면 자율 학습에 대해 말을 전부
there's any any questions
어떤 질문이있다
what does what is going on here
여기에 무엇을 무슨 일이야 않습니다
yeah so the question is are you may be literate linear rising the bedroom space
그래 그래서 질문은 당신이 침실 공간을 상승 글을 읽고 선형 될 수 있습니다
and that's maybe one way to think about it that here we remember we're just
그리고 우리는 우리가있어 기억 여기에 그것에 대해 생각하는 한 가지 방법은 어쩌면이다
sampling program just sampling from noise and passing them through the
샘플링 프로그램을 바로 잡음에서 샘플링과를 통해 전달
discriminator rather through the generator and then the generator has
판별보다는 제너레이터 후 발전기 갖는다
just decided to use these different noises channels in nice ways such that
바로 그런 그 좋은 방법으로 서로 다른 소리 채널을 사용하기로 결정
if you interplay between the noise you end up interpolating between the images
당신이 소음 사이에 상호 작용하는 경우는 이미지 사이에 보간 결국
in sort of a nice smooth way so hopefully that lets you know that it's
수 그래서 잘하면 좋은 부드러운 방법의 종류에 당신은 그것의 알고
not just sort of memorizing training examples it's actually wanting to
그저 실제로 싶은 연수 예를 기억하지
generalize from him in a nice way right so just to recap everything we talked
바로 그래서 그냥 우리가 이야기 모든 것을 정리해하는 좋은 방법으로 그 일반화
about today we gave you a lot of really useful practical tips for working with
약 오늘 우리는 작업을위한 당신에게 정말 유용한 실용적인 팁을 많이 준
videos and then I give you a lot of very non practical tips for generating
동영상은 내가 당신에게 발생하는 매우 비 실용적인 팁을 많이 제공
beautiful images so I think this stuff is really cool but I'm not sure what the
아름다운 이미지가 그래서 나는이 물건은 정말 멋진 생각하지만 난 무엇 확실하지 않다
uses other than generating images but its cool so it's fun and definitely
생성 된 이미지 이외의 사용하지만 그 멋진 그것은 재미와 확실히 있도록
stick around next time because we'll have a guest lecture from jap teen so if
우리는 JAP 대에서 게스트 강의를해야하기 때문에 다음에 주위에 붙어 그렇다면
you're watching on the internet maybe you might wanna come to class for that
당신은 그것을 위해 클래스에 와서 인터넷에 아마 당신은 싶어 있습니다보고있어
one so I think that's everything we have today and see you guys later
하나는 그래서 나는 그것이 오늘날 우리가 모든 것을 생각하고 나중에 너희들을 볼